Experience O
: O
June B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
September I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Currently O
working O
as O
React B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Techwave B-ORG

Mariia B-PER
Hoikhman I-PER
from O
Zhytomyr, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Egor B-PER
Vakulenko I-PER

Larysa B-PER
Khomenko I-PER
graduated O
from O
Vadym B-ORG
Hetman I-ORG
Kyiv I-ORG
National I-ORG
Economic I-ORG
University I-ORG

Skills O
: O
System B-SKILL
Administration I-SKILL
, O
Firewall B-SKILL
, O
Web B-SKILL
servers I-SKILL
, O
Mail B-SKILL
Servers I-SKILL
, O
Linux B-SKILL

Embroidery B-PROF
Digitizer I-PROF

Kostiantyn B-PER
Baidush I-PER
worked O
as O
PHP B-PROF
| I-PROF
JavaScript I-PROF
Software I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
Twizted B-ORG
Design I-ORG
from O
Feb B-DATE
2014 I-DATE
Jan I-DATE
2016 I-DATE

Senior B-PROF
.Net I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
React B-SKILL
and O
AWS B-SKILL
and O
Docker B-SKILL

Dmytro B-PER
Andrushchenko I-PER
worked O
as O
SEO B-PROF
Specialist I-PROF
at O
Oracle B-ORG

Pyasetskiy B-PER
Nazar I-PER
is O
a O
PC B-PROF
sales I-PROF
manager I-PROF
based O
in O
Lviv B-LOC
region I-LOC

Experience O
: O
July B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
July I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

FRONTEND B-PROF
DEVELOPER I-PROF

Software B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
(Contract) I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Github B-SKILL
Actions I-SKILL
and O
Docker B-SKILL
Compose I-SKILL
and O
Pytest B-SKILL

Python B-PROF
Team I-PROF
Lead I-PROF
Freelance I-PROF

Worked O
at O
Calmerry B-ORG
in O
USA B-LOC
01/2020 B-DATE
07/2021 I-DATE

BigData B-PROF
DevOps I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF

Technical O
expertise O
: O
HTML B-SKILL
, O
Composer B-SKILL
, O
Figma B-SKILL
, O
Kanban B-SKILL

Studied O
at O
Odessa B-ORG
College I-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Technologies I-ORG
"Server" I-ORG

IT B-PROF
Recruiter I-PROF

Front-end B-PROF
developer I-PROF

Ievgen B-PER
Korobytskyi I-PER

Experience O
: O
February B-DATE
2015 I-DATE
February I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Tony B-PER
(Katsu) I-PER
Dai I-PER
worked O
as O
Blockchain B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
& I-PROF
Project I-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
eagoats B-ORG

Worked O
at O
Multiplex B-ORG
in O
Kyiv B-LOC
2010-2013 B-DATE

Oliinykov B-PER
Valentin I-PER
worked O
as O
Electronics B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
MiCON B-ORG
Systems I-ORG

Recruiter B-PROF
at O
Webzool B-ORG
Creative I-ORG
Inc I-ORG
from O
06/2022 B-DATE
10/2022 I-DATE

Skills O
: O
Animate B-SKILL
, O
plugins B-SKILL
Red I-SKILL
Giant I-SKILL
, O
Lightroom B-SKILL
, O
Adobe B-SKILL
Character I-SKILL
Animator I-SKILL
, O
Cinema B-SKILL
4D I-SKILL

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Ajax B-SKILL
, O
SonarQube B-SKILL
, O
Quickbook B-SKILL
, O
C# B-SKILL

Studied O
at O
Hillel B-ORG
IT I-ORG
School I-ORG

Worked O
at O
RISE B-ORG
Public I-ORG
Company I-ORG
in O
Kyiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC
08/2014 B-DATE
01/2015 I-DATE

Experience O
: O
11/2019 B-DATE
10/2021 I-DATE

ЄВГЕН B-PER
УРСУЛЯК I-PER

OLEKSII B-PER
SKORUK I-PER
is O
a O
UX/UI B-PROF
Designer, I-PROF
Team I-PROF
Leader I-PROF
based O
in O
Kyiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Web B-PROF
UX/UI I-PROF
Designer I-PROF

Technical B-PROF
support I-PROF

Studied O
at O
Ivan B-ORG
Franko I-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Lviv I-ORG

YEVHENII B-PER
DEMCHENKO I-PER
worked O
as O
PROJECT B-PROF
MANAGER I-PROF
at O
Hillel B-ORG
company I-ORG

Pavlo B-PER
Konopada I-PER
worked O
as O
Flutter B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
Freelance I-PROF
at O
Conreality B-ORG
from O
JUN B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Present I-DATE

Паша B-PER
Шпичко I-PER
worked O
as O
Ведущий B-PROF
визуальный I-PROF
мерчандайзер I-PROF
at O
SANAHUNT B-ORG

Technical O
expertise O
: O
SCSS B-SKILL
, O
Typescript B-SKILL
, O
CSS B-SKILL
, O
HTML B-SKILL

Shamil B-PER
Isayev I-PER
worked O
as O
FRONTEND B-PROF
DEVELOPER I-PROF
at O
Freelance B-ORG
from O
09/2020 B-DATE
05/2021 I-DATE

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Practice B-SKILL
of I-SKILL
meeting I-SKILL
deadlines I-SKILL
, O
data B-SKILL
mining I-SKILL
, O
Analytical B-SKILL
, O
Effective B-SKILL
team I-SKILL
work I-SKILL

Experience O
: O
Nov B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
Present I-DATE

Oleksandr B-PER
Miklosh I-PER
worked O
as O
Junior B-PROF
Manual I-PROF
QA I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
Inshop B-ORG
Group I-ORG
sp. I-ORG
z I-ORG
o.o. I-ORG

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Slack B-SKILL
, O
DevTools B-SKILL
, O
REST B-SKILL
API I-SKILL
testing I-SKILL

Project B-PROF
Manager I-PROF

Currently O
working O
as O
Senior B-PROF
Angular I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
(Contractual) I-PROF
at O
Marakisoft B-ORG
Technologies I-ORG
Pvt.Ltd.Co I-ORG

Skills O
: O
ES5 B-SKILL
, O
Axios B-SKILL
, O
RestAPI B-SKILL
, O
NestJS B-SKILL
, O
JavaScript B-SKILL

work B-PROF
in I-PROF
IT I-PROF
company I-PROF

Yaseen B-PER
Zain I-PER
worked O
as O
Concept B-PROF
Artist I-PROF
[Internship] I-PROF
at O
Centre B-ORG
for I-ORG
Content I-ORG
Creation I-ORG

Aleksei B-PER
Kutin I-PER
is O
a O
assistant B-PROF
to I-PROF
the I-PROF
chief I-PROF
engineer I-PROF
based O
in O
The B-LOC
TV I-LOC
channel I-LOC
"Kiev" I-LOC

Skills O
: O
HTML5 B-SKILL
, O
GithubAction B-SKILL
, O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Redis B-SKILL
, O
Docker B-SKILL

Skills O
: O
React.js B-SKILL
, O
PHP B-SKILL
, O
JQuery B-SKILL
, O
CSS3 B-SKILL
, O
Canvas B-SKILL

Trainee B-PROF
DevOps I-PROF

Skills O
: O
Code B-SKILL
Review I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript B-SKILL
, O
Integration B-SKILL
Testing I-SKILL
, O
API B-SKILL
, O
JavaScript/jQuery B-SKILL

Studied O
at O
National B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Kyiv-Mohyla I-ORG
Academy I-ORG
(Kyiv) I-ORG

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Go B-SKILL
, O
RabbitMQ B-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL B-SKILL
, O
GraphQL B-SKILL

Frontent B-PROF
Web I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
Vue.js I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
HTML B-SKILL
and O
JavaScript B-SKILL
and O
Nuxt.js B-SKILL

Associate B-PROF
Designer I-PROF
at O
XPRESS B-ORG
PAYMENT I-ORG
SOLUTIONS I-ORG
LIMITED I-ORG
from O
Apr B-DATE
2023-Present I-DATE

Worked O
at O
4IRE B-ORG
in O
Istanbul, B-LOC
Turkey I-LOC
04/2019 B-DATE
11/2019 I-DATE

FRONT-END B-PROF
DEVELOPER I-PROF

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Bloc B-SKILL
, O
HTTPS B-SKILL
, O
Design B-SKILL
Patterns I-SKILL
, O
KISS B-SKILL

Experience O
: O
April B-DATE
2016 I-DATE
October I-DATE
2016 I-DATE

CEO B-PROF

Sergey B-PER
Shynkarenko I-PER
worked O
as O
Markup B-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
wwwest.solutions B-ORG

Kostyshen B-PER
Pavlo I-PER
worked O
as O
Test B-PROF
website I-PROF
at O
4fr B-ORG
from O
April B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
NOW I-DATE

Studied O
at O
The B-ORG
Donbas I-ORG
State I-ORG
Engineering I-ORG
Academy I-ORG

Rasim B-PER
Karimli I-PER
from O
Baku B-LOC

Experience O
: O
Aug. B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Jan I-DATE
2023 I-DATE

Currently O
working O
as O
Senior B-PROF
Product I-PROF
Manager I-PROF
for I-PROF
AI I-PROF
Compliance I-PROF
Platform I-PROF
at O
Bridgewater B-ORG
Associates I-ORG

MYKHAIL B-PER
worked O
as O
FULL-STACK B-PROF
DEVELOPER I-PROF
at O
ISQUAD B-ORG

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Photoshop B-SKILL
, O
BEM B-SKILL
, O
SQL B-SKILL
Basics I-SKILL
, O
Flexbox B-SKILL

Skills O
: O
Adaptability B-SKILL
, O
Communication B-SKILL
, O
Time B-SKILL
Management I-SKILL
, O
Leadership B-SKILL
, O
Team B-SKILL
Work I-SKILL

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Avro B-SKILL
Schema I-SKILL
Definition I-SKILL
, O
Spring B-SKILL
MVC I-SKILL
, O
Protocol B-SKILL
Buffer I-SKILL
, O
K8S B-SKILL

Yullia B-PER
Ivanchuk I-PER

Concept B-PROF
artist, I-PROF
UI/UX I-PROF
designer I-PROF

Менеджер B-PROF
по I-PROF
работе I-PROF
с I-PROF
контрагентами I-PROF
at O
NDA B-ORG
from O
Июль B-DATE
2017 I-DATE
январь I-DATE
2018 I-DATE

Yelena B-PER
Ignateva I-PER
worked O
as O
Automation B-PROF
QA I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
IGNATEVA B-ORG
from O
January B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
September I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Senior B-PROF
Marketing I-PROF
Manager I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Analytics B-SKILL
and O
User B-SKILL
Acquisition I-SKILL
and O
Marketing B-SKILL

Ievgen B-PER
Korobytskyi I-PER
is O
a O
Product B-PROF
owner I-PROF
based O
in O
Kiev B-LOC

Freelance B-PROF
Web I-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Canvas B-SKILL
, O
Avocode B-SKILL
, O
MacOS B-SKILL
, O
Redux B-SKILL

Currently O
working O
as O
Co-founder B-PROF
& I-PROF
COO I-PROF
at O
Express B-ORG
Auto I-ORG
Body I-ORG
Parts I-ORG

Technical B-PROF
support I-PROF
engineer I-PROF
at O
HUBBER B-ORG
from O
03.2021 B-DATE
until I-DATE
now I-DATE

QA B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF

Alexander B-PER
Kolomoyets I-PER
worked O
as O
freelance B-PROF
at O
PintaWebWare B-ORG

Project B-PROF
coordinator I-PROF
at O
Nestle B-ORG
Business I-ORG
Customer I-ORG
Service I-ORG
from O
2021 B-DATE

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Semrush B-SKILL
, O
HTML B-SKILL
, O
Google B-SKILL
Ads I-SKILL
, O
English B-SKILL
philology I-SKILL

IT B-PROF
Senior I-PROF
Brand I-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
LLC B-ORG
Sanofi-Aventis I-ORG
Ukraine I-ORG
from O
2020 B-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Developer B-PROF
at O
dProfile B-ORG
from O
May B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
June I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Experience O
: O
2019 B-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Hailemaryam B-PER
Mecca I-PER
Feyisa I-PER
worked O
as O
Owner B-PROF
of I-PROF
the I-PROF
start I-PROF
up I-PROF
at O
Piasa B-ORG
Promotion I-ORG
and I-ORG
Events I-ORG
from O
June-2020 B-DATE
January I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

TYMUR B-PER
MORGUN I-PER
from O
Kyiv B-LOC

Studied O
at O
Azerbaijan B-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University I-ORG

Software B-PROF
Testing I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF

Studied O
at O
Pasha B-ORG
Bank I-ORG
Product I-ORG
School I-ORG

Technical O
expertise O
: O
React B-SKILL
Router I-SKILL
, O
Segment B-SKILL
, O
Nest.js B-SKILL
, O
MySql B-SKILL

Anna B-PER
Karp I-PER
from O
Odessa, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Worked O
at O
Mobidev B-ORG
in O
Kharkiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC
11/2020 B-DATE
Present I-DATE

Worked O
at O
UNIVERSAL B-ORG
auto I-ORG
in O
Kyiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC
6 B-DATE
month I-DATE

Plastics B-PROF
manufacturing I-PROF
plant I-PROF
worker I-PROF

Experience O
: O
11.2021-6.2022 B-DATE

Experience O
: O
04/2020 B-DATE
03/2021 I-DATE

Front-end B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
MobX B-SKILL
and O
Jest B-SKILL
and O
Bootstrap B-SKILL

Digital B-PROF
Marketing I-PROF
Specialist I-PROF

Business B-PROF
Analyst I-PROF

Skills O
: O
Eureka B-SKILL
, O
Code B-SKILL
Review I-SKILL
, O
Camunda B-SKILL
BPMN I-SKILL
, O
Hibernate B-SKILL
, O
Spring B-SKILL
Boot I-SKILL

Studied O
at O
Master B-ORG
in I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science I-ORG
Data I-ORG
Scientist I-ORG
WSB I-ORG
University I-ORG

Junior B-PROF
Android I-PROF
(Kotlin/Java) I-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Vladyslav B-PER
Skintiyan I-PER

Intermediate B-PROF
Customer I-PROF
Support I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF

Experience O
: O
Oct B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
Oct I-DATE
2020 I-DATE

Illya B-PER
Shkurko I-PER
from O
London, B-LOC
England I-LOC

Olena B-PER
Boychuk I-PER
worked O
as O
Automation B-PROF
QA I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
PineSoftweare B-ORG
from O
January B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
to I-DATE
February I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Experience O
: O
09/2012 B-DATE
09/2013 I-DATE

Vladyslav B-PER
Yelizarov I-PER
worked O
as O
Project B-PROF
manager, I-PROF
Head I-PROF
of I-PROF
Department I-PROF
at O
Clinics B-ORG
Up I-ORG
(IT I-ORG
product I-ORG
company) I-ORG
from O
Jan B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
Nov I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Worked O
at O
Obozrevatel B-ORG
media I-ORG
in O
Ukraine B-LOC
March B-DATE
2016 I-DATE
September I-DATE
2018 I-DATE

Skills O
: O
HTML5 B-SKILL
, O
Adobe B-SKILL
XD I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript B-SKILL
, O
Git B-SKILL
, O
CSS3 B-SKILL

Front-end B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Satraps B-ORG
from O
December B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Present I-DATE

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Scrum B-SKILL
, O
Click B-SKILL
Up I-SKILL
, O
Jira B-SKILL
, O
Project B-SKILL
Management I-SKILL

Marketing B-PROF
analyst I-PROF

Senior B-PROF
Software I-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Experience O
: O
October B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
till I-DATE
now I-DATE

Katsu B-PER
(Tony) I-PER
Dai I-PER
from O
CANNAVIGIA B-LOC

Mykhailo B-PER
Pasichnyk I-PER
worked O
as O
ML B-PROF
RESEARCHER I-PROF
at O
Luxoft B-ORG
from O
Sep2022-Jan2023 B-DATE

SERHII B-PER
SHEPTYTSKYI I-PER

Currently O
working O
as O
Junior B-PROF
DevOps I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
ENESTECH B-ORG

Skills O
: O
risk B-SKILL
analysis I-SKILL
, O
Jupyter B-SKILL
Notebook I-SKILL
, O
SQL B-SKILL
, O
fundamental B-SKILL
analysis I-SKILL
, O
credit B-SKILL
analysis I-SKILL

MARTUSENKO B-PER
SERGEY I-PER

Assistant B-PROF
at O
METRO B-ORG
CASH I-ORG
& I-ORG
CARRY I-ORG
from O
2020 B-DATE
JANUARY I-DATE
2021 I-DATE
MARCH I-DATE

MURAD B-PER
ISMAYILOV I-PER
from O
Baku, B-LOC
AZ I-LOC

Worked O
at O
Pecode B-ORG
in O
Lviv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC
December B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
Present I-DATE

Elvin B-PER
Mammadli I-PER
is O
a O
Frontend B-PROF
React I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
based O
in O
Azerbaijan B-LOC

YULIIA B-PER
NAZARENKOVA I-PER

Web B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Experience O
: O
2020 B-DATE

Currently O
working O
as O
E-COMMERCE B-PROF
at O
NDA B-ORG
(DAIRO I-ORG
PROJECT) I-ORG

Architect/System B-PROF
Administrator I-PROF

YELYZAVETA B-PER
KISENKO I-PER
graduated O
from O
Ukrainian B-ORG
Catholic I-ORG
University I-ORG

OPEYEMI B-PER
JOHN I-PER
ILESANMI I-PER

Serg B-PER
ey I-PER
Kuch I-PER
nskyi I-PER
graduated O
from O
University B-ORG
of I-ORG
Customs I-ORG
and I-ORG
Finance I-ORG

Skills O
: O
Hibernate B-SKILL
, O
JUnit B-SKILL
, O
Angular B-SKILL
, O
JavaScript B-SKILL
, O
AWS B-SKILL

Junior B-PROF
Java I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
UTA B-ORG
from O
July B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
July I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Sissay B-PER
Wube I-PER
worked O
as O
Intern B-PROF
Junior I-PROF
IT I-PROF
Officer I-PROF
at O
Milto B-ORG
Labs I-ORG
PLC I-ORG

Currently O
working O
as O
Software B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
Intern I-PROF
at O
Vengreso B-ORG
Inc I-ORG

Studied O
at O
Beetroot B-ORG
Academy I-ORG

Anna B-PER
Sumtsova I-PER

Worked O
at O
IT B-ORG
Video I-ORG
Production I-ORG
company I-ORG
in O
Lviv B-LOC
February B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
January I-DATE
2023 I-DATE

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Sketch B-SKILL
, O
Jira B-SKILL
, O
Сonsumer B-SKILL
psychology I-SKILL
, O
Java B-SKILL

Dmytro B-PER
Dolbilov I-PER
graduated O
from O
National B-ORG
Aviation I-ORG
University I-ORG

AFFILIATE B-PROF
MANAGER I-PROF

C++ B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Sergey B-PER
Tararay I-PER
worked O
as O
Freelancer B-PROF
(C# I-PROF
/ I-PROF
Java) I-PROF
at O
Transexpo B-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
from O
Dec B-DATE
2013 I-DATE
Nov I-DATE
2016 I-DATE

KHRYSTYNA B-PER
STOKOLOSA I-PER
from O
Kraków, B-LOC
Poland I-LOC

Mykola B-PER
Kholtobin I-PER

Software B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Labrin B-ORG
from O
February B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
July I-DATE
2020 I-DATE

Samir B-PER
Rzayev I-PER
is O
a O
Data B-PROF
analyst I-PROF
based O
in O
Baku, B-LOC
Azerbaijan I-LOC

Currently O
working O
as O
Automation B-PROF
QA I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
Zazmic B-ORG

Skills O
: O
Figma B-SKILL
, O
After B-SKILL
Effect I-SKILL
, O
Photoshop B-SKILL
, O
CSS B-SKILL
, O
InDesign B-SKILL

Кухарев B-PER
Марк I-PER
Игоревич I-PER
from O
UK B-LOC

Currently O
working O
as O
Developer B-PROF
at O
GlobalLogic B-ORG

Worked O
at O
Coca-Cola B-ORG
Bottlers I-ORG
Azerbaijan I-ORG
in O
Baku, B-LOC
Azerbaijan I-LOC
July B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
November I-DATE
2018 I-DATE

Viacheslav B-PER
Pasholok I-PER
worked O
as O
Construction B-PROF
engineer I-PROF
at O
Fart-Bud B-ORG
from O
May B-DATE
2015 I-DATE
Nov I-DATE
2016 I-DATE

Frontend B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Maksym B-PER
Koloda I-PER
worked O
as O
Full B-PROF
Stack I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
UDC B-ORG
Software I-ORG

Worked O
at O
Alfa-Bank B-ORG
in O
Kharkiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC
10.2020 B-DATE
to I-DATE
present I-DATE
time I-DATE

Oleksandr B-PER
Lavrusenko I-PER
worked O
as O
FRONT B-PROF
END I-PROF
DEVELOPER I-PROF
at O
Ammazing B-ORG
Apps I-ORG
(Welltech) I-ORG

Batychko B-PER
Sophie I-PER
graduated O
from O
WHYTE B-ORG
SMM I-ORG

Experience O
: O
SEP B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
DEC I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Experience O
: O
JAN B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
NOW I-DATE

Currently O
working O
as O
Full B-PROF
stack I-PROF
web I-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
Awery B-ORG
Aviation I-ORG
Software I-ORG

Worked O
at O
TWIN B-ORG
WIN I-ORG
GAMES I-ORG
in O
Kyiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC
2020 B-DATE
present I-DATE

Studied O
at O
Киевский B-ORG
Политехнический I-ORG
Институт I-ORG

Web B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Head B-PROF
of I-PROF
IT I-PROF
Project I-PROF
Management I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Spring B-SKILL
and O
Cisco B-SKILL
and O
ISO B-SKILL
27001 I-SKILL

Anduamlak B-PER
Berhanu I-PER
is O
a O
Senior B-PROF
Software I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
based O
in O
Addis B-LOC
Ababa, I-LOC
Ethiopia I-LOC

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Google B-SKILL
Docs I-SKILL
, O
Snov.io B-SKILL
, O
SMM B-SKILL
, O
Power B-SKILL
Point I-SKILL

Ruslan B-PER
Khusainov I-PER
graduated O
from O
Bachelor B-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
science I-ORG

Experience O
: O
1 B-DATE
year I-DATE

Full-stack B-PROF
web I-PROF
developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
CSS B-SKILL
and O
Debugger B-SKILL
and O
Django B-SKILL

Experience O
: O
Sep B-DATE
2006 I-DATE
Dec I-DATE
2006 I-DATE

Full B-PROF
Stack I-PROF
(PHP, I-PROF
JS) I-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Worked O
at O
Bliscore B-ORG
in O
Lviv B-LOC
9 B-DATE
months I-DATE

Sales B-PROF
manager, I-PROF
merchandiser I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Change B-SKILL
Management I-SKILL
and O
Budget B-SKILL
Management I-SKILL
and O
B2B B-SKILL
marketing I-SKILL

Skills O
: O
Vscode B-SKILL
, O
Docker B-SKILL
, O
GIT B-SKILL
, O
Angular B-SKILL
, O
Kafka B-SKILL

Litvinova B-PER
Daria I-PER
from O
Ukraine, B-LOC
Kyiv I-LOC

Skills O
: O
MongoDB B-SKILL
, O
TypeScript B-SKILL
, O
Redux B-SKILL
, O
Tailwind B-SKILL
, O
Redux-saga B-SKILL

Developer, B-PROF
QA I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
Levtech B-ORG
from O
08/2020 B-DATE
03/2021 I-DATE

Andrei B-PER
Vorona I-PER
worked O
as O
Assistant B-PROF
to I-PROF
the I-PROF
restaurant I-PROF
director I-PROF
at O
McDonald’s B-ORG

Middle B-PROF
Automation I-PROF
QA I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Testing B-SKILL
Theory I-SKILL
and O
Cypress.io B-SKILL
and O
XPath B-SKILL

trainee/junior B-PROF
React I-PROF
developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
NextJS B-SKILL
and O
NodeJs B-SKILL
and O
RTK B-SKILL
query I-SKILL

Business B-PROF
Analyst I-PROF
at O
SteelKiwi B-ORG
inc I-ORG
from O
August B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
August I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Maxim B-PER
Martinyuk I-PER

Skills O
: O
Linux B-SKILL
, O
Nginx B-SKILL
, O
XDebug B-SKILL
, O
PHP B-SKILL
, O
Webhoock B-SKILL

Project B-PROF
manager I-PROF

Serhii B-PER
Liahera I-PER
graduated O
from O
KOROLYOV B-ORG
ZHYTOMYR I-ORG
MILITARY I-ORG
INSTITUTE I-ORG

Front-end B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
(React) I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
react-query B-SKILL
and O
react-test-library B-SKILL
and O
vue B-SKILL

Technical O
expertise O
: O
MVP B-SKILL
, O
Epics B-SKILL
, O
Entrepreneurship B-SKILL
, O
A/B B-SKILL
Testing I-SKILL

Assistant B-PROF
in I-PROF
economic I-PROF
analysis I-PROF

Skills O
: O
VS B-SKILL
Code I-SKILL
, O
Bulma B-SKILL
, O
Trello B-SKILL
, O
English B-SKILL
, O
React B-SKILL

Web B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Binom B-SKILL
and O
Sketch B-SKILL
and O
Linux B-SKILL

NodeJs B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
HebronSoft B-ORG
from O
11/2020 B-DATE
04/2021 I-DATE

NARGIS B-PER
ISMAYILOVA I-PER
is O
a O
FrontEndDeveloper B-PROF
based O
in O
Osaka, B-LOC
Japan I-LOC

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Azure B-SKILL
portal I-SKILL
, O
EF B-SKILL
, O
Scrum B-SKILL
, O
HTML B-SKILL

Studied O
at O
Code B-ORG
Academy I-ORG

Kyrylo B-PER
Onofriichuk I-PER
is O
a O
php B-PROF
developer I-PROF
based O
in O
Kyiv B-LOC

Vorobiova B-PER
Anastasiia I-PER
is O
a O
Front-end B-PROF
developer I-PROF
based O
in O
EPAM B-LOC
Systems I-LOC

web B-PROF
developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Golang B-SKILL
1.16+ I-SKILL
and O
Kafka B-SKILL
and O
NoSQL B-SKILL
(Redis, I-SKILL
MongoDB, I-SKILL
ElasticSearch) I-SKILL

Skills O
: O
Off-page B-SKILL
SEO I-SKILL
, O
Composite B-SKILL
materials I-SKILL
, O
On-page B-SKILL
SEO I-SKILL
, O
Digital B-SKILL
marketing I-SKILL
strategy I-SKILL
, O
High B-SKILL
technology I-SKILL
machining I-SKILL
systems I-SKILL

UI/UX B-PROF
Designer I-PROF

Lead B-PROF
Software I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF

Head B-PROF
of I-PROF
Department I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
analytics B-SKILL
and O
control B-SKILL
of I-SKILL
deadlines I-SKILL
and O
project B-SKILL
management I-SKILL

Experience O
: O
2021 B-DATE
2023 I-DATE

Artur B-PER
Sydorenko I-PER
graduated O
from O
National B-ORG
Law I-ORG
University I-ORG

Skills O
: O
Windows B-SKILL
, O
Collections B-SKILL
, O
Linux/Bash B-SKILL
, O
Russian B-SKILL
, O
Git B-SKILL

Viacheslav B-PER
Pasholok I-PER
graduated O
from O
Kyiv B-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Construction I-ORG
and I-ORG
Architecture, I-ORG
automatization I-ORG
and I-ORG
information I-ORG
faculty, I-ORG
Project I-ORG
Management. I-ORG
Master’s I-ORG
degree I-ORG

Front-end B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Worked O
at O
PepsiCo B-ORG
Ukraine I-ORG
in O
US B-LOC
2022-2022 B-DATE

Motion B-PROF
Designer, I-PROF
3D I-PROF
Artist I-PROF
at O
Upwork B-ORG
from O
sep. B-DATE
2009 I-DATE
feb. I-DATE
2011 I-DATE

Рекрутер B-PROF

Worked O
at O
Nortal B-ORG
in O
Kyiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC
10.2019 B-DATE
09.2021 I-DATE

QA B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Datagrip B-SKILL
and O
Jira B-SKILL
and O
Technical B-SKILL
Specification I-SKILL
Analysis I-SKILL

AI B-PROF
Software I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
& I-PROF
Project I-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
CANNAVIGIA B-ORG
from O
Feb B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
May I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Daria B-PER
Shapoval I-PER
worked O
as O
SMM B-PROF
specialist I-PROF
at O
DotBig B-ORG

ILKIN B-PER
GULUZADA I-PER

Denis B-PER
Volokhovskyi I-PER
graduated O
from O
Dnipropetrovsk B-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG

Alina B-PER
Sushylova I-PER
is O
a O
Teacher B-PROF
based O
in O
Odessa, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Experience O
: O
Feb B-DATE
2012 I-DATE
Jun I-DATE
2013 I-DATE

Project/Product B-PROF
Manager I-PROF

QA B-PROF
and I-PROF
Data I-PROF
Research I-PROF
contributor I-PROF
at O
Edvantis B-ORG
from O
01.2019 B-DATE
present I-DATE

Pavlo B-PER
Stakhiv I-PER
worked O
as O
Sr. B-PROF
Project I-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
SoftServe, B-ORG
Inc I-ORG
from O
May B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
May I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Junior B-PROF
Product I-PROF
Owner I-PROF
at O
Ernst B-ORG
& I-ORG
Young I-ORG
Azerbaijan I-ORG
from O
September B-DATE
2021- I-DATE
Present I-DATE

LEAD B-PROF
FULL-STACK I-PROF
WEB I-PROF
DEVELOPER I-PROF

Currently O
working O
as O
WordPress B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
DevIT B-ORG

Junior B-PROF
Java I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Globallogic B-ORG
from O
February B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
June I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Skills O
: O
Angular B-SKILL
2+ I-SKILL
, O
Twig B-SKILL
, O
JS B-SKILL
, O
Redis B-SKILL
, O
CSS B-SKILL

OLEKSII B-PER
SUBBOTIN I-PER
is O
a O
Manager B-PROF
based O
in O
Ukraine, B-LOC
Kyiv I-LOC

Artem B-PER
Sharapanyk I-PER
worked O
as O
React B-PROF
Native I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Exandria B-ORG

Worked O
at O
ITStep B-ORG
in O
ПриватБанк B-LOC
з B-DATE
березня I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Worked O
at O
Gebeya B-ORG
in O
Remote B-LOC
Jan B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
Oct I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Experience O
: O
02/2020 B-DATE
to I-DATE
07/2021 I-DATE

Front-end B-PROF
developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
English B-SKILL
(intermediate) I-SKILL
and O
Bootstrap B-SKILL
and O
CSS B-SKILL

Manual B-PROF
QA I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
GitBash B-SKILL
and O
UAT B-SKILL
and O
ECP B-SKILL

Devops B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF

Сергій B-PER
Акименко I-PER
is O
a O
Дизайнер B-PROF
based O
in O
Київ B-LOC

Worked O
at O
ПАТ B-ORG
"БАНК I-ORG
ФОРУМ" I-ORG
in O
Україна B-LOC
2010 B-DATE
2019 I-DATE

Kovalev B-PER
Denis I-PER
worked O
as O
PHP/Golang B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Sunstones.ua B-ORG

Sergey B-PER
Bubelo I-PER
is O
a O
Sales B-PROF
manager I-PROF
based O
in O
Vinnytsia B-LOC

Dmitry B-PER
Klymenko I-PER
worked O
as O
Senior B-PROF
web I-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
Softengi B-ORG
from O
2018 B-DATE
2020 I-DATE

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Asana B-SKILL
, O
Zeplin B-SKILL
, O
Trello B-SKILL
, O
Figma B-SKILL

Project B-PROF
manager I-PROF

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Git/Git B-SKILL
flow I-SKILL
, O
MongoDB B-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL B-SKILL
, O
Redis B-SKILL

Oleksandra B-PER
Pidvysotska I-PER
graduated O
from O
Kyiv B-ORG
National I-ORG
Economic I-ORG
University, I-ORG
Kyiv I-ORG

Dmytro B-PER
Kudrynskyi I-PER
worked O
as O
Python B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Upwork B-ORG
from O
Sep B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
current I-DATE

Vladyslav B-PER
Yelizarov I-PER
is O
a O
Project B-PROF
manager I-PROF
based O
in O
Odesa, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Arthur B-PER
Agabekyan I-PER
worked O
as O
Owner B-PROF
of I-PROF
at O
Arabella B-ORG
coffee I-ORG
from O
2021 B-DATE

Experience O
: O
June B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
May I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

HAMID B-PER
BALABAYLI I-PER
worked O
as O
Senior B-PROF
.NET I-PROF
Backend I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Unibank B-ORG
ASC I-ORG
KB I-ORG
from O
2016 B-DATE
2019 I-DATE

OLEKSII B-PER
SKORUK I-PER
worked O
as O
UX B-PROF
Designer I-PROF
at O
DotBig B-ORG
from O
MARCH B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
MAY I-DATE
2020 I-DATE

PM B-PROF
Assistant I-PROF
(proofreader, I-PROF
editor) I-PROF

Vovnenko B-PER
Anton I-PER
from O
Ukraine B-LOC

Middle B-PROF
React I-PROF
Front I-PROF
End I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
CSS B-SKILL
and O
Nuxt B-SKILL
and O
Vuex B-SKILL

Experience O
: O
November B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
October I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

ARTEM B-PER
HURSKYI I-PER
graduated O
from O
Kyiv B-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Culture I-ORG
and I-ORG
Arts I-ORG

Igor B-PER
Deyneka I-PER
is O
a O
Advisor B-PROF
to I-PROF
the I-PROF
General I-PROF
Director I-PROF
based O
in O
Kyiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Currently O
working O
as O
QA B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
Ambo B-ORG
University I-ORG

Junior B-PROF
Full I-PROF
Stack I-PROF
.NET I-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Преподаватель B-PROF
английского I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Adobe B-SKILL
Photoshop I-SKILL
and O
C# B-SKILL
and O
HTML B-SKILL

Anna B-PER
Solnyshkina I-PER
worked O
as O
UI&UX B-PROF
Designer I-PROF
at O
Artsense B-ORG
from O
September B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
December I-DATE
2023 I-DATE

Skills O
: O
Sublime B-SKILL
Text I-SKILL
, O
Ember B-SKILL
, O
Typescript B-SKILL
, O
jQuery B-SKILL
, O
Angular B-SKILL

Experience O
: O
Nov B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
May I-DATE
2023 I-DATE

Web B-PROF
and I-PROF
Mobile I-PROF
application I-PROF
testing I-PROF
at O
GLOBALLOGIC B-ORG
from O
10.2021 B-DATE
Present I-DATE

Alisa B-PER
Russu I-PER
worked O
as O
Account B-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
Site-ok B-ORG

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Contacts B-SKILL
, O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Autolayout B-SKILL
, O
UiTable B-SKILL

Currently O
working O
as O
Software B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
Developia B-ORG
Engineering I-ORG

Artur B-PER
Karapetyan I-PER
worked O
as O
Android B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Etnetera B-ORG
from O
01/03/2016– B-DATE
30/06/2016 I-DATE

Art B-PROF
Director I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Illustrator B-SKILL
and O
Redmine B-SKILL
and O
Autodesk B-SKILL
Maya I-SKILL

Experience O
: O
Oct B-DATE
2017 I-DATE
Nov I-DATE
2018 I-DATE

Arthur B-PER
Hakobyan I-PER
graduated O
from O
Yerevan B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG
Faculty I-ORG
of I-ORG
Informatics I-ORG
and I-ORG
Applied I-ORG
Mathematics I-ORG

Skills O
: O
Microservices B-SKILL
, O
OOP B-SKILL
, O
Redis B-SKILL
, O
Hibernate B-SKILL
ORM I-SKILL
, O
Spring B-SKILL
Security I-SKILL

Full-stack B-PROF
web I-PROF
developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Sass B-SKILL
and O
JS B-SKILL
and O
MySQL B-SKILL

Hailemaryam B-PER
Mecca I-PER
Feyisa I-PER
worked O
as O
Developer B-PROF
III I-PROF
at O
Melkite B-ORG
Vas I-ORG
from O
August-2020 B-DATE
February I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Project B-PROF
manager I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
KanBan B-SKILL
and O
Jira B-SKILL
and O
Scrum B-SKILL

Arthur B-PER
Hakobyan I-PER
worked O
as O
Front-End B-PROF
Web I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
ACBA B-ORG
Credit I-ORG
Agricole I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
CJSC I-ORG
from O
1 B-DATE
year I-DATE
(2020 I-DATE
2021) I-DATE

Vladyslav B-PER
Demydov I-PER
from O
Кременчуг, B-LOC
Полтавская I-LOC
область, I-LOC
Украина I-LOC

Worked O
at O
Training B-ORG
Center I-ORG
of I-ORG
Trade I-ORG
Unions I-ORG
in O
Chernihiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC
JANUARY B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
NOW I-DATE

community-manager B-PROF

Freelance B-PROF
Front-end I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
TYPESCRIPT B-SKILL
and O
REACT B-SKILL
and O
REDUX B-SKILL

Product B-PROF
Manager I-PROF
& I-PROF
Data I-PROF
Scientist I-PROF

Data B-PROF
Analyst I-PROF

Roksolana B-PER
Tokarevych I-PER
from O
Ivano-frankivsk, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Experience O
: O
Mar'18-Jan'20 B-DATE

B B-PER
A I-PER
H I-PER
R I-PER
A I-PER
M I-PER
B I-PER
A I-PER
Y I-PER
R I-PER
A I-PER
M I-PER
L I-PER
I I-PER

Skills O
: O
Pascal B-SKILL
, O
CSS B-SKILL
, O
HTML B-SKILL
, O
Angular B-SKILL
2 I-SKILL
, O
SASS B-SKILL

Senior B-PROF
UX/UI I-PROF
Designer I-PROF

Legacy B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Technical O
expertise O
: O
GitHub B-SKILL
, O
Bootstrap B-SKILL
, O
GitLab B-SKILL
, O
TypeScript B-SKILL

Dmitriy B-PER
Zelinskiy I-PER
is O
a O
.NET B-PROF
Backend I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
based O
in O
Odessa B-LOC

Studied O
at O
Kyiv B-ORG
State I-ORG
Institute I-ORG
of I-ORG
Applied I-ORG
Arts I-ORG
and I-ORG
Design I-ORG
named I-ORG
after I-ORG
Myckhailo I-ORG
Boichuk I-ORG

Frontend B-PROF
developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
JavaScript B-SKILL
and O
Visual B-SKILL
Studio I-SKILL
Code I-SKILL
and O
Bootstrap B-SKILL

Web B-PROF
development I-PROF

Studied O
at O
Хмельницький B-ORG
кооперативний I-ORG
коледж I-ORG
Хмельницького I-ORG
торговельно-економічного I-ORG
інституту I-ORG

Worked O
at O
Elektron B-ORG
Hökumətin I-ORG
İnkişafı I-ORG
Mərkəzi I-ORG
/ I-ORG
e-Gov I-ORG
Development I-ORG
Center I-ORG
in O
Baku, B-LOC
Azerbaijan I-LOC
Jun B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
Present I-DATE

Software B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF

Berdnyk B-PER
Mykhailo I-PER
is O
a O
Python B-PROF
/ I-PROF
Django I-PROF
back-end I-PROF
developer I-PROF
based O
in O
Kharkiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Worked O
at O
Luxoft B-ORG
USA I-ORG
Inc. I-ORG
in O
Kyiv, B-LOC
UA I-LOC
01.12.2013-30.06.2016 B-DATE

Iryna B-PER
Mykhaylyshyn I-PER

Mykyta B-PER
Lysenko I-PER

Skills O
: O
техническая B-SKILL
настройка I-SKILL
компьютерной I-SKILL
техники I-SKILL
, O
настройка B-SKILL
Smart I-SKILL
телевизоров I-SKILL
, O
работа B-SKILL
с I-SKILL
базой I-SKILL
данных I-SKILL
1С I-SKILL
, O
работа B-SKILL
с I-SKILL
программным I-SKILL
обеспечением I-SKILL
Package I-SKILL
Assistant I-SKILL
, O
техническая B-SKILL
поддержка I-SKILL

junior B-PROF
front-end I-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
Skalar B-ORG
from O
February B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
October I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Worked O
at O
Druk B-ORG
Art I-ORG
in O
Chernivtsi, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC
March B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
September I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Experience O
: O
Листопад B-DATE
2014–жовтень I-DATE
2016 I-DATE

Ksyonz B-PER
David I-PER
graduated O
from O
SkillUP B-ORG

ZAYIKA B-PER
VLADIMIR I-PER
ALEKSANDROVICH I-PER
worked O
as O
Seller B-PROF
of I-PROF
non-food I-PROF
products I-PROF
at O
Shop B-ORG
«GAP» I-ORG
from O
2011 B-DATE
2012 I-DATE

Khrystyna B-PER
Tserkovna I-PER
is O
a O
An B-PROF
operator I-PROF
on I-PROF
the I-PROF
website I-PROF
of I-PROF
the I-PROF
online I-PROF
store I-PROF
based O
in O
Lviv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Fiddle B-SKILL
, O
DHC B-SKILL
Rest I-SKILL
Client I-SKILL
, O
Crashlytics B-SKILL
, O
Amazon B-SKILL
SDK I-SKILL
Tester I-SKILL

C++ B-PROF
Software I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Perforce B-SKILL
and O
Boost B-SKILL
and O
MacOS B-SKILL

Studied O
at O
Obafemi B-ORG
Awolowo I-ORG
University I-ORG

Experience O
: O
Jun B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
Jan I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Olga B-PER
Bordiug I-PER

Samir B-PER
Rzayev I-PER
graduated O
from O
Koç B-ORG
University I-ORG
Erasmus I-ORG
Exchange I-ORG
Program I-ORG

ELVIN B-PER
RZAYEV I-PER
worked O
as O
Procurement B-PROF
and I-PROF
Supply-Chain I-PROF
Management I-PROF
Analyst I-PROF
Intern I-PROF
at O
Japan B-ORG
Tobacco I-ORG
International I-ORG

Software B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
WinForms B-SKILL
and O
WCF B-SKILL
and O
NUnit B-SKILL

Worked O
at O
Luxoft B-ORG
in O
Kiev B-LOC
6 B-DATE
month I-DATE

Front-End B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Next B-SKILL
and O
CSS B-SKILL
and O
Docker B-SKILL

Network B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF

UX/UI B-PROF
designer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Graphic B-SKILL
Design I-SKILL
and O
Wireframing B-SKILL
& I-SKILL
Prototyping I-SKILL
and O
Visual B-SKILL
Communication I-SKILL

Andrei B-PER
Vorona I-PER
worked O
as O
Assistant B-PROF
to I-PROF
the I-PROF
restaurant I-PROF
director I-PROF
at O
McDonald’s B-ORG

Lesia B-PER
Veretnyk I-PER
from O
Ivano-Frankivsk B-LOC

Mykhailo B-PER
Yurchenko I-PER
worked O
as O
UX/UI B-PROF
& I-PROF
Product I-PROF
Designer I-PROF
at O
Navoto.com B-ORG

Currently O
working O
as O
FRONT-END B-PROF
DEVELOPER I-PROF
at O
Company B-ORG
INC I-ORG

Dmytro B-PER
Tovstokoryi I-PER
worked O
as O
Front-end B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
(Vue I-PROF
/ I-PROF
Nuxt I-PROF
/ I-PROF
React I-PROF
/ I-PROF
Next) I-PROF
at O
Woolf B-ORG
from O
mar. B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
may I-DATE
2023 I-DATE

Currently O
working O
as O
Junior B-PROF
Unity I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
globalfreelance.ua B-ORG

System B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
/Team I-PROF
Leader I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Kafka B-SKILL
and O
AWS B-SKILL
and O
Android B-SKILL
Studio I-SKILL

HANNA B-PER
OZERIANSKA I-PER
graduated O
from O
National B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Kyiv-Mohyla I-ORG
Academy I-ORG

Igor B-PER
Kostiuchenko I-PER
worked O
as O
Frontend B-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
Gamzix B-ORG

Sales B-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
Эффект B-ORG
Нова I-ORG
from O
Nov B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
Present I-DATE

Studied O
at O
Simon B-ORG
Kuznets I-ORG
Kharkiv I-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Economics I-ORG

Technical O
expertise O
: O
MySQL B-SKILL
, O
PHP B-SKILL
, O
Wordpress B-SKILL
, O
HTML-CSS B-SKILL

Skills O
: O
Scrum B-SKILL
, O
Project B-SKILL
management I-SKILL
, O
Business B-SKILL
analysis I-SKILL
, O
Requirements B-SKILL
management I-SKILL
, O
Internal B-SKILL
audits I-SKILL

Stanislav B-PER
Kirkilevsky I-PER
graduated O
from O
Kyiv B-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Technology I-ORG
and I-ORG
Design I-ORG

VASIL B-PER
TELIACHUK I-PER
worked O
as O
Category B-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
LARIS B-ORG
from O
May B-DATE
2015 I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

PHP B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Arthur B-PER
Agabekyan I-PER
from O
USA B-LOC

Technology B-PROF
Expert I-PROF

Operational B-PROF
Manager I-PROF

Dmytro B-PER
Stepanov I-PER
worked O
as O
Developer B-PROF
at O
Altum B-ORG
Agency I-ORG
from O
December B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
May I-DATE
2023 I-DATE

Olesia B-PER
Salamakha I-PER

Experience O
: O
03.2020 B-DATE
03.2022 I-DATE

Dmytro B-PER
Kruhlov I-PER
worked O
as O
QA B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
Yalantis B-ORG

YURII B-PER
ZARIPA I-PER
from O
Kyiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Illya B-PER
Shkurko I-PER
worked O
as O
Software B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
Intern I-PROF
at O
Kvazar-Micro B-ORG
from O
Jun B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
Jun I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Nikita B-PER
Kharlamov I-PER

FIFINA B-PER
KSENIA I-PER
graduated O
from O
KYIV B-ORG
NATIONAL I-ORG
ECONOMICS I-ORG
UNIVERSITY I-ORG

Zainab B-PER
Adewunmi I-PER

Experience O
: O
31/10/2018 B-DATE
30/06/2021 I-DATE

Front-end B-PROF
developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Webpack B-SKILL
and O
Next.js B-SKILL
and O
React B-SKILL

Ivana B-PER
Frankivsk I-PER
worked O
as O
SMM B-PROF
Specialist I-PROF
at O
Forbytes B-ORG
from O
December B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
March I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Anduamlak B-PER
Berhanu I-PER
graduated O
from O
HiLCoE B-ORG
School I-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technology I-ORG

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Typescript B-SKILL
, O
CSS3 B-SKILL
, O
HTML5 B-SKILL
, O
Github B-SKILL

Waleed B-PER
Bin I-PER
Khalid I-PER
worked O
as O
Sales B-PROF
Representative I-PROF
at O
Freelance/Different B-ORG
Companies I-ORG

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Level B-SKILL
design I-SKILL
, O
Adobe B-SKILL
Photoshop I-SKILL
, O
Adobe B-SKILL
Illustrator I-SKILL
, O
Figma B-SKILL

Skills O
: O
Bootstrap B-SKILL
, O
Scrum B-SKILL
, O
GIT B-SKILL
, O
HTML B-SKILL
, O
Git B-SKILL

Full B-PROF
stack I-PROF
developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
PostgreSQL B-SKILL
and O
Linters B-SKILL
(ESLint, I-SKILL
Prettier) I-SKILL
and O
Nest.js B-SKILL

Aliyev B-PER
Tural I-PER
graduated O
from O
Baku B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG

Associate B-PROF
Designer I-PROF

Serhii B-PER
Musiienko I-PER
graduated O
from O
National B-ORG
Agricultural I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ukraine I-ORG

Skills O
: O
Retail B-SKILL
, O
Communication B-SKILL
, O
Mobile B-SKILL
Application I-SKILL
Design I-SKILL
, O
User-centered B-SKILL
Design I-SKILL
, O
Branding B-SKILL

Ksyonz B-PER
David I-PER

Portfolio B-PROF
analyst I-PROF

ANDRII B-PER
SUSALIEV I-PER
from O
Kyiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Tale B-PER
Abayev I-PER

Sales B-PROF
Representative I-PROF

Evgeniy B-PER
Onopriienko I-PER
worked O
as O
QA B-PROF
engineer I-PROF
at O
Zazmic B-ORG
from O
March B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Present I-DATE

Project B-PROF
Manager I-PROF
/ I-PROF
Scrum I-PROF
Master I-PROF
at O
Devtorium B-ORG
from O
September B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
July I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Studied O
at O
Interregional B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Personnel I-ORG
Management I-ORG

Pylypchuk B-PER
Artem I-PER
worked O
as O
Middle B-PROF
Front-end I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Innovations B-ORG
Development I-ORG
Lab I-ORG

Experience O
: O
06/2022 B-DATE
Present I-DATE

OFFICE B-PROF
MANAGER I-PROF

ANTON B-PER
OKHMUSH I-PER
worked O
as O
Analytics B-PROF
and I-PROF
information I-PROF
department I-PROF
specialist I-PROF
at O
CTP B-ORG
English I-ORG
School I-ORG

Skills O
: O
Jenkins B-SKILL
, O
Azure B-SKILL
, O
Java B-SKILL
, O
Terraform B-SKILL
, O
Vault B-SKILL

YEVHENII B-PER
DEMCHENKO I-PER

Currently O
working O
as O
Leadgen B-PROF
/ I-PROF
Sales I-PROF
manager I-PROF
at O
Aimtraction B-ORG
agency I-ORG

Kateryna B-PER
Kanaeva I-PER
worked O
as O
Web B-PROF
designer I-PROF
at O
Erbis B-ORG
from O
Feb B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
currently I-DATE

Tech B-PROF
lead I-PROF

Skills O
: O
YouTrack B-SKILL
, O
Burndown B-SKILL
, O
KanBan B-SKILL
, O
Gantt B-SKILL
, O
Jira B-SKILL

Senior B-PROF
Software I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
Kvazar-Micro B-ORG
from O
Jun B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
Present I-DATE

Yaroslav B-PER
Dembitskyi I-PER
worked O
as O
Embroidery B-PROF
Digitizer I-PROF
at O
SoftServe B-ORG
from O
January B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
to I-DATE
April I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Data B-PROF
analyst I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
BI B-SKILL
intelligence I-SKILL
and O
Data B-SKILL
mining I-SKILL
and O
Tableau B-SKILL

Currently O
working O
as O
Scrum B-PROF
master I-PROF
at O
Yuzhnoye B-ORG
Design I-ORG
Office I-ORG

Skills O
: O
Node.js B-SKILL
, O
Android B-SKILL
Studio I-SKILL
, O
Flutter B-SKILL
, O
Visual B-SKILL
Studio I-SKILL
Code I-SKILL
, O
MySQL B-SKILL

J B-PER
A I-PER
R I-PER
O I-PER
S I-PER
L I-PER
A I-PER
V I-PER
I I-PER
O I-PER
N I-PER
O I-PER
V I-PER
is O
a O
Freelance B-PROF
designer I-PROF
based O
in O
Kyiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Olga B-PER
Hutsuluk I-PER
worked O
as O
Head B-PROF
of I-PROF
Contract I-PROF
Department I-PROF
at O
IT B-ORG
School I-ORG
GoIT I-ORG

Sissay B-PER
Wube I-PER
worked O
as O
Software B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
Sheger B-ORG
Mass I-ORG
Transport I-ORG
Enterprise I-ORG
from O
August B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
Present I-DATE

Studied O
at O
Obafemi B-ORG
Awolowo I-ORG
University, I-ORG
Ile-Ife, I-ORG
Nigeria I-ORG

Studied O
at O
Lyceum B-ORG
"Naokova I-ORG
zmina" I-ORG

Experience O
: O
June B-DATE
2022–till I-DATE
present I-DATE

QA B-PROF
Manual I-PROF
(IoT) I-PROF
/ I-PROF
Junior I-PROF
Project I-PROF
Manager I-PROF

H B-PER
A I-PER
I I-PER
D I-PER
A I-PER
I I-PER
A I-PER
N I-PER
A I-PER
S I-PER
T I-PER
A I-PER
S I-PER
I I-PER
I I-PER
A I-PER
is O
a O
HR B-PROF
MANAGER I-PROF
based O
in O
Kyiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Data B-PROF
analyst I-PROF

Vadym B-PER
Kushnir I-PER
worked O
as O
Software B-PROF
engineer/Team I-PROF
leader I-PROF
at O
Planarry B-ORG
from O
November B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
January I-DATE
2019 I-DATE

Software B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Micro B-SKILL
Services I-SKILL
and O
Spring B-SKILL
Security I-SKILL
and O
Redis B-SKILL
DB I-SKILL

Inbound B-PROF
Sales I-PROF
Marketing I-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
IntellectEU B-ORG
from O
June B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Present I-DATE

Operational B-PROF
director I-PROF

Worked O
at O
ARTCUBE B-ORG
in O
Kyiv B-LOC
Jun B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
May I-DATE
2023 I-DATE

Worked O
at O
Codevog B-ORG
in O
Kharkiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC
12/2020 B-DATE
04/2022 I-DATE

Shabelnyk B-PER
Mykhailo I-PER
graduated O
from O
Mykhailo B-ORG
Ostrohradskyi I-ORG
Kremenchuk I-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG

Project B-PROF
Manager I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Word B-SKILL
and O
Jira B-SKILL
and O
Firebase B-SKILL

Event B-PROF
Manager I-PROF
Assistant I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
SDLC B-SKILL
and O
Web B-SKILL
development I-SKILL
and O
Time B-SKILL
Management I-SKILL

Content B-PROF
Manager I-PROF

Kanan B-PER
Suleymanli I-PER

Experience O
: O
2016 B-DATE
2018 I-DATE

Denis B-PER
Konieiev I-PER

Danil B-PER
Starovoitov I-PER
is O
a O
strong B-PROF
junior I-PROF
front-end I-PROF
developer I-PROF
based O
in O
Kharkiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Swagger B-SKILL
, O
Mantis B-SKILL
, O
Usability B-SKILL
testing I-SKILL
, O
Manual B-SKILL
testing I-SKILL

Aliona B-PER
Krepko I-PER
graduated O
from O
Bila B-ORG
Tserkva I-ORG
National I-ORG
Agrarian I-ORG
University I-ORG

Currently O
working O
as O
NodeJs B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
HebronSoft B-ORG

Tetiana B-PER
Gordynska I-PER
worked O
as O
Private B-PROF
English I-PROF
translator I-PROF
at O
N-iX B-ORG

Currently O
working O
as O
Software B-PROF
Tester I-PROF
at O
Conduit B-ORG
Realworld I-ORG

Key B-PROF
Business I-PROF
Development I-PROF
Manager I-PROF
/ I-PROF
Marketing I-PROF
specialist I-PROF
at O
Lantera B-ORG
from O
DECEMBER B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
SEPTEMBER I-DATE
2020 I-DATE

Currently O
working O
as O
Fullstack B-PROF
Software I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Unibank B-ORG
ASC I-ORG

Currently O
working O
as O
Software B-PROF
Tester I-PROF
at O
Uz.gov.ua B-ORG

Project B-PROF
Manager I-PROF

Skills O
: O
Agile B-SKILL
Methodology I-SKILL
, O
MySQL B-SKILL
, O
Stakeholder B-SKILL
Management I-SKILL
, O
React B-SKILL
, O
Risk B-SKILL
Management I-SKILL

Oleh B-PER
Davymuka I-PER
worked O
as O
Python B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Simple2B B-ORG

Scrum B-PROF
Master I-PROF

Viktor B-PER
Filippov I-PER
is O
a O
Customer B-PROF
support I-PROF
based O
in O
Odessa, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Data B-PROF
analyst I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Microsoft B-SKILL
PowerPoint I-SKILL
and O
Task B-SKILL
deliverer I-SKILL
and O
Stata B-SKILL

Illia B-PER
Horevoi I-PER
worked O
as O
iOS B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Expoplatform B-ORG

Currently O
working O
as O
Front-end B-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
EPAM B-ORG
Systems I-ORG

Experience O
: O
JANUARY B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
NOW I-DATE

Worked O
at O
Kvazar-Micro B-ORG
in O
Kyiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC
Nov B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
Jun I-DATE
2020 I-DATE

ROBERT B-PER
PALANDZHIAN I-PER
graduated O
from O
Kharkiv B-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Radioelectronics I-ORG

Oleh B-PER
Hrytsyk I-PER
graduated O
from O
Ukrainian B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Printing I-ORG

Studied O
at O
LemonSchool- B-ORG
course I-ORG
Web I-ORG
design I-ORG
(Figma) I-ORG

Bolshak B-PER
Serhii I-PER
worked O
as O
Analyst B-PROF
specialist I-PROF
at O
Comfy B-ORG
Trade I-ORG
LLC I-ORG
from O
06.2019 B-DATE
11.2019 I-DATE

Full B-PROF
Stack I-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Senior B-PROF
Software I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF

Studied O
at O
Zaporizhzhya B-ORG
National I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University I-ORG

Senior B-PROF
Software I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF

Currently O
working O
as O
CUSTOMER B-PROF
CARE I-PROF
REPRESENTATIVE I-PROF
at O
Sahad B-ORG
Stores I-ORG

Skills O
: O
User B-SKILL
Research I-SKILL
, O
Web B-SKILL
Design I-SKILL
, O
Figma B-SKILL
, O
Photoshop B-SKILL
, O
Illustrator B-SKILL

Ulug'bek B-PER
Yo'lchimurodov I-PER
graduated O
from O
Najot B-ORG
Ta'lim I-ORG

Karen B-PER
Minasyan I-PER
graduated O
from O
Certificate B-ORG
of I-ORG
Completion I-ORG
demo I-ORG
lab I-ORG
Veeam I-ORG
Availability I-ORG
Suite I-ORG
8x I-ORG
Administration I-ORG

Senior B-PROF
Front I-PROF
End I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Technaura B-ORG
Systems I-ORG
GMBH I-ORG
from O
04/2022–11/2022 B-DATE

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Xstream B-SKILL
, O
Ansible B-SKILL
Tower I-SKILL
, O
CSS B-SKILL
selectors I-SKILL
, O
HTML B-SKILL

Experience O
: O
2019-2022 B-DATE

Ramin B-PER
Nasreddinzade I-PER

Technical O
expertise O
: O
SpaCy B-SKILL
, O
TensorFlow B-SKILL
, O
Flask B-SKILL
, O
Jupyter B-SKILL

Experience O
: O
февраля B-DATE
2009 I-DATE
марта I-DATE
2010 I-DATE

Experience O
: O
NOVEMBER B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
PRESENT I-DATE

Balovnev B-PER
Dmitriy I-PER
is O
a O
Full B-PROF
Stack I-PROF
(PHP, I-PROF
JS) I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
based O
in O
Kiev B-LOC

Shop-assistant B-PROF
at O
TSUM B-ORG
Kyiv I-ORG
from O
2016 B-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Skills O
: O
TypeScript B-SKILL
, O
PHP B-SKILL
, O
Git B-SKILL
, O
CSS3 B-SKILL
, O
NodeJS B-SKILL

Savchenko B-PER
Mykyta I-PER
from O
Ukraine B-LOC

Alexey B-PER
Bashmakow I-PER
from O
Dnipro, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Experience O
: O
03/2001 B-DATE
04/2002 I-DATE

Oleh B-PER
Meserenko I-PER
worked O
as O
Front B-PROF
End I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Code B-ORG
Generation I-ORG
Software I-ORG

Currently O
working O
as O
Python B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
ucode B-ORG
IT I-ORG
Academy I-ORG

MAKSYM B-PER
SHARKO I-PER
graduated O
from O
National B-ORG
University I-ORG
Lviv I-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG

Svitlana B-PER
Konovalova I-PER
worked O
as O
Project B-PROF
manager I-PROF
and I-PROF
data I-PROF
analyst I-PROF
at O
Jagiellonian B-ORG
University I-ORG
in I-ORG
Krakow I-ORG

Trainee B-PROF
Xamarin I-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Roman B-PER
Dorosh I-PER
is O
a O
Python B-PROF
Back-end I-PROF
developer I-PROF
based O
in O
Uvik B-LOC
Software I-LOC

Skills O
: O
CSS B-SKILL
, O
ООП B-SKILL
, O
JavaScript B-SKILL
(ES5, I-SKILL
ES6) I-SKILL
, O
Zeplin B-SKILL
, O
Angular B-SKILL
Material I-SKILL

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Adobe B-SKILL
Photoshop I-SKILL
, O
Invision B-SKILL
, O
Graphic B-SKILL
Design I-SKILL
, O
Sketch B-SKILL

Sergej B-PER
Miroshnichenko I-PER
worked O
as O
Front-end B-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
Krivoy B-ORG
Rog I-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG

React/NodeJS B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
addons B-SKILL
and O
Puppeteer B-SKILL
and O
formik B-SKILL

Frontend/Web B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
JavaScript B-SKILL
(ES6+) I-SKILL
and O
PUG B-SKILL
and O
HTML B-SKILL

Worked O
at O
EPAM B-ORG
in O
Lviv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC
October B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
March I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Docker B-SKILL
, O
Gitlab B-SKILL
, O
Jenkins B-SKILL
, O
Linux B-SKILL

Front B-PROF
End I-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Studied O
at O
Academy B-ORG
of I-ORG
Public I-ORG
Administration I-ORG
under I-ORG
the I-ORG
President I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Republic I-ORG
of I-ORG
Azerbaijan I-ORG
(Baku, I-ORG
Azerbaijan) I-ORG

Senior B-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at I-PROF
the I-PROF
regional I-PROF
IT I-PROF
infrastructure I-PROF
at O
Ukrainian B-ORG
Radio I-ORG
Systems I-ORG
Beeline I-ORG
UA I-ORG
from O
2012 B-DATE
2013 I-DATE

SALES B-PROF
MANAGER I-PROF
at O
Ekonomika+ B-ORG
from O
June B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
May I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Technical O
expertise O
: O
HTML5 B-SKILL
, O
CSS B-SKILL
, O
CSS3 B-SKILL
, O
Squarespace B-SKILL

Sanan B-PER
Mammadov I-PER
graduated O
from O
Baku B-ORG
Higher I-ORG
Oil I-ORG
School I-ORG

Currently O
working O
as O
Project B-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
FlexGear B-ORG

Trainee B-PROF
Manual I-PROF
QA I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
Optyks B-ORG
from O
2 B-DATE
years I-DATE

Developer B-PROF

Trainee B-PROF
FullStack I-PROF
at O
CactusEra B-ORG
from O
03/2021 B-DATE
05/2021 I-DATE

.NET B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
EPAM B-ORG
Systems I-ORG
from O
Apr B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
Mar I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Currently O
working O
as O
Full-Stack B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
BroSolution B-ORG

Viktor B-PER
Burenin I-PER
from O
Competera B-LOC

Sergey B-PER
Bubelo I-PER
worked O
as O
Sales B-PROF
development I-PROF
representative I-PROF
at O
Collect B-ORG
Reviews I-ORG

Yevhen B-PER
Yarovyi I-PER
worked O
as O
Business B-PROF
Analyst I-PROF
at O
PJSC B-ORG
«Russian I-ORG
Standard I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
» I-ORG
from O
Feb B-DATE
2014 I-DATE
Feb I-DATE
2016 I-DATE

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Figma B-SKILL
, O
Mockups B-SKILL
, O
User B-SKILL
flow I-SKILL
, O
Prototyping B-SKILL

E B-PER
M I-PER
A I-PER
D I-PER
H I-PER
A I-PER
M I-PER
A I-PER
D I-PER
worked O
as O
Senior B-PROF
Front-end I-PROF
engineer I-PROF
at O
Manage-Yours B-ORG

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Communicative B-SKILL
, O
Data B-SKILL
analysis I-SKILL
, O
Concept B-SKILL
sketches I-SKILL
, O
Flexible B-SKILL

Python B-PROF
Back-end I-PROF
developer I-PROF

Skills O
: O
Oracle B-SKILL
, O
Asp.Net B-SKILL
, O
Dapper B-SKILL
, O
Javascript B-SKILL
, O
Blazor B-SKILL

Front-End B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Ведущий B-PROF
менеджер I-PROF
отдела I-PROF
ВЭД I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
написание B-SKILL
технической I-SKILL
и I-SKILL
пользовательской I-SKILL
документации I-SKILL
and O
работа B-SKILL
в I-SKILL
Google I-SKILL
Docs, I-SKILL
Confluence, I-SKILL
Jira I-SKILL
and O
гибкость B-SKILL

Experience O
: O
March B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Present I-DATE

senior B-PROF
Java I-PROF
developer I-PROF

SEO B-PROF
SPECIALIST I-PROF

Studied O
at O
Dnipro B-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Railway I-ORG
Transport I-ORG

Oleksandr B-PER
Honcharov I-PER
worked O
as O
Full-Stack B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Freelance B-ORG

Backend B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Viktoriia B-PER
Volyanska I-PER

TARAS B-PER
BROVCHENKO I-PER
worked O
as O
PHP B-PROF
Software I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
Andersen B-ORG
Lab I-ORG
from O
01/2022 B-DATE
01/2023 I-DATE

Alexandra B-PER
Gortopan I-PER
worked O
as O
Business B-PROF
Intelligence I-PROF
Project I-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
Bridge B-ORG
from O
September B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
February I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Skills O
: O
Linkedin B-SKILL
, O
boolean B-SKILL
search I-SKILL
, O
Djinni B-SKILL
, O
X-ray B-SKILL
, O
Turbo B-SKILL
Haring I-SKILL

Karyna B-PER
Vakar I-PER
graduated O
from O
UX/UI B-ORG
Design I-ORG
at I-ORG
Beetroot I-ORG
Academy I-ORG

Yurii B-PER
Mamurko I-PER
is O
a O
Own B-PROF
Projects I-PROF
based O
in O
Ukraine B-LOC

Skills O
: O
Redux B-SKILL
, O
Rest B-SKILL
API I-SKILL
, O
Tailwind B-SKILL
CSS I-SKILL
, O
HTML B-SKILL
, O
Solid B-SKILL

Vladyslav B-PER
Yuskiv I-PER
worked O
as O
Full-Stack B-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
Logika B-ORG

Experience O
: O
August B-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Angular B-SKILL
10 I-SKILL
, O
AWS B-SKILL
, O
SCSS B-SKILL
, O
Angular B-SKILL
9 I-SKILL

Senior B-PROF
Big I-PROF
Data I-PROF
engineer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Kafka B-SKILL
and O
Grafana B-SKILL
and O
Spark B-SKILL

NIGAR B-PER
ALIZADA I-PER
is O
a O
Data B-PROF
base I-PROF
administrator I-PROF
based O
in O
Baku, B-LOC
Azerbaijan I-LOC

Currently O
working O
as O
BI B-PROF
analyst I-PROF
at O
Bulls B-ORG
Media I-ORG

Web B-PROF
Analyst I-PROF
at O
Odessa B-ORG
Debate I-ORG
Union I-ORG
from O
2017-2018 B-DATE

Backend B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
(Contract) I-PROF

Self B-PROF
employed I-PROF

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Diagrams.net B-SKILL
, O
ClickUp B-SKILL
, O
Microsoft B-SKILL
Office I-SKILL
, O
Figma B-SKILL

Software B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF

Anastasiia B-PER
Babachenko I-PER
worked O
as O
Frontend B-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
Chikrizova B-ORG
Temy I-ORG

Back-End B-PROF
developer I-PROF

Product B-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
FN.UA B-ORG
from O
03.2009-07.2009 B-DATE

Studied O
at O
Web B-ORG
Designer I-ORG
(Genius I-ORG
Space) I-ORG

IT B-PROF
Project I-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
Private B-ORG
joint-stock I-ORG
company I-ORG
Kyiv-Dniprovske I-ORG
interbranch I-ORG
industrial I-ORG
enterprise I-ORG
of I-ORG
railway I-ORG
transport I-ORG
from O
April B-DATE
2022-December I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Painter B-PROF
/ I-PROF
2D I-PROF
Artist I-PROF

Middle B-PROF
at O
XCDS B-ORG
from O
2018-2019 B-DATE

Skills O
: O
HTML B-SKILL
, O
PHP B-SKILL
, O
TypeScript B-SKILL
, O
JavaScript B-SKILL
, O
CSS B-SKILL

Experience O
: O
October B-DATE
2017 I-DATE
till I-DATE
March I-DATE
2020 I-DATE

Studied O
at O
National B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Kyiv-Mohyla I-ORG
Academy I-ORG

Studied O
at O
College B-ORG
of I-ORG
Communications I-ORG
and I-ORG
Informatization I-ORG
Ukrain, I-ORG
Odessa I-ORG

Worked O
at O
Max B-ORG
Grill I-ORG
in O
Avenga B-LOC
March B-DATE
2022–June I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Fullstack B-PROF
Javascript I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
REST B-SKILL
and O
HTML B-SKILL
& I-SKILL
CSS I-SKILL
and O
GRAPHQL B-SKILL

Skills O
: O
analytics B-SKILL
, O
photoshop B-SKILL
, O
ux/ui B-SKILL
, O
web/desktop B-SKILL
, O
principle B-SKILL

.NET/WPF B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
(Remote I-PROF
work) I-PROF

NARMIN B-PER
ALIYEVA I-PER

Technical O
expertise O
: O
SCRUM B-SKILL
, O
defect B-SKILL
tracking I-SKILL
, O
Postman B-SKILL
, O
STLC B-SKILL

Terekhov B-PER
Dmytro I-PER
is O
a O
System B-PROF
Administrator I-PROF
based O
in O
Dnipro, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Backend B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Myroslava B-PER
Zapisochna I-PER

Anna B-PER
Vorobiova I-PER
is O
a O
PMO B-PROF
analyst I-PROF
based O
in O
Kyiv B-LOC

Worked O
at O
Ista-Center B-ORG
LLC I-ORG
in O
Dnipropetrovs’k, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC
09/2013 B-DATE
09/2014 I-DATE

Zaur B-PER
Mammadov I-PER
worked O
as O
Accounting B-PROF
Analyst I-PROF
Internship I-PROF
at O
Finnair B-ORG

Currently O
working O
as O
Full B-PROF
Stack I-PROF
(PHP, I-PROF
JS) I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Global B-ORG
Partner I-ORG
Soft I-ORG

Front-end B-PROF
developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Angular B-SKILL
2 I-SKILL
and O
Pascal B-SKILL
and O
Materialize B-SKILL
CSS I-SKILL

IOS B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Колесников B-PER
Александр I-PER
Александрович I-PER
is O
a O
Junior B-PROF
Python I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
based O
in O
Харьков B-LOC

Graphic B-PROF
& I-PROF
UI I-PROF
Designer I-PROF

UI/UX B-PROF
& I-PROF
Motion I-PROF
designer I-PROF
at O
Step B-ORG
to I-ORG
dream I-ORG
agency I-ORG
from O
April B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
December I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Oleksii B-PER
Subbotin I-PER
worked O
as O
Junior B-PROF
Project I-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
OSKI B-ORG
Solutions I-ORG
from O
April B-DATE
2007 I-DATE
February I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Experience O
: O
11/2018 B-DATE
03/2019 I-DATE

Experience O
: O
Jan B-DATE
2016 I-DATE
Sep I-DATE
2016 I-DATE

Software B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Angular B-SKILL
and O
Microsoft B-SKILL
Azure I-SKILL
and O
Vue B-SKILL
JS I-SKILL

Currently O
working O
as O
iOS B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
AppliKey B-ORG
Solutions I-ORG

Studied O
at O
Yaroslav B-ORG
Mudryi I-ORG
National I-ORG
Law I-ORG
University, I-ORG
Kharkiv I-ORG

Software B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF

UX/UI B-PROF
Designer I-PROF

Valeriia B-PER
Honcharuck I-PER
from O
Ukraine B-LOC

Simon B-PER
El I-PER
Mansoury I-PER
graduated O
from O
KPI B-ORG
University I-ORG
Faculty I-ORG
of I-ORG
informatic I-ORG
and I-ORG
calculated I-ORG
technologies I-ORG

Kolesnyk B-PER
Dmytro I-PER
Viktorovich I-PER
worked O
as O
.NET B-PROF
C# I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Learning B-ORG
Something I-ORG
from O
2001 B-DATE
2007 I-DATE

Worked O
at O
CHI B-ORG
Software I-ORG
in O
Kyiv B-LOC
July B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
present I-DATE
time I-DATE

React-Native B-PROF
apps I-PROF
developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Three-JS B-SKILL
and O
Bootstrap B-SKILL
and O
GitHub B-SKILL

Svetlana B-PER
Cholovskaya I-PER
is O
a O
UX/UI B-PROF
Designer I-PROF
based O
in O
kyiv, B-LOC
ukraine I-LOC

Worked O
at O
Zelenin B-ORG
Lab I-ORG
in O
Lodz, B-LOC
Poland I-LOC
February B-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Java B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Senior B-PROF
Data I-PROF
Analyst I-PROF

Business B-PROF
Analyst I-PROF

Technical O
expertise O
: O
My B-SKILL
SQL I-SKILL
, O
JavaScript B-SKILL
Frameworks I-SKILL
, O
Kendo B-SKILL
UI I-SKILL
, O
MuleSoft B-SKILL
API I-SKILL

Experience O
: O
24/11/2021 B-DATE
01/04/2022 I-DATE

Financial B-PROF
Manager I-PROF

Experience O
: O
01.02.2021- B-DATE
15.04.2022 I-DATE

Middle B-PROF
Java I-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Igor B-PER
Kostiuchenko I-PER
from O
Kyiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Avocado B-SKILL
, O
HTML5 B-SKILL
, O
GitHub B-SKILL
, O
Figma B-SKILL

Valeriia B-PER
Laricheva I-PER
is O
a O
UX/UI B-PROF
Designer I-PROF
based O
in O
Lisbon B-LOC

Technical O
expertise O
: O
XP B-SKILL
, O
GraphQL B-SKILL
, O
GAAP B-SKILL
, O
Java B-SKILL

Skills O
: O
Bootstrap B-SKILL
, O
TexturePacker B-SKILL
, O
DOM B-SKILL
, O
Visual B-SKILL
Studio I-SKILL
Code I-SKILL
, O
SASS B-SKILL

Marchuk B-PER
Ievgen I-PER
worked O
as O
Android B-PROF
mobile I-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
Samsung B-ORG
Electronics I-ORG
from O
2015 B-DATE
2016 I-DATE

Perch B-PER
Darbinyan I-PER
is O
a O
MARKETING B-PROF
STRATEGIST I-PROF
based O
in O
Spain B-LOC

Java B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Менеджер B-PROF
маркетплейсів I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Google B-SKILL
Документи I-SKILL
and O
Microsoft B-SKILL
Office I-SKILL
and O
Касова B-SKILL
дисципліна I-SKILL

Skills O
: O
CRM B-SKILL
Optima I-SKILL
, O
GDP B-SKILL
, O
Kaizen B-SKILL
, O
MS B-SKILL
Office I-SKILL
, O
Scrum B-SKILL

SHVE B-PER
TS I-PER
DENIS I-PER
ANATOLIEVICH I-PER
worked O
as O
Senior B-PROF
Android I-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
Nullgravity B-ORG
from O
Sept B-DATE
2012 I-DATE
Mar I-DATE
2015 I-DATE

Currently O
working O
as O
Project B-PROF
manager I-PROF
at O
SmartA.agency B-ORG

Studied O
at O
Addis B-ORG
Ababa I-ORG
University I-ORG

FRONTEND B-PROF
DEVELOPER I-PROF

Skills O
: O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Kanban B-SKILL
, O
Jira B-SKILL
, O
regression B-SKILL
testing I-SKILL
, O
Sourcetree B-SKILL

Technical O
expertise O
: O
ETL B-SKILL
, O
hypothesis B-SKILL
testing I-SKILL
, O
product B-SKILL
requirements I-SKILL
, O
Data B-SKILL
Mapping I-SKILL

Illya B-PER
Shkurko I-PER
worked O
as O
Senior B-PROF
Software I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
BSS B-ORG
Ukraine I-ORG

Kosianchuk B-PER
Dmytro I-PER
graduated O
from O
Taras B-ORG
Shevchenko I-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG

Technical O
expertise O
: O
SQL B-SKILL
, O
SSRS B-SKILL
, O
TSQL B-SKILL
, O
SSIS B-SKILL

Digital-маркетолог B-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
E-mail B-SKILL
маркетинг I-SKILL
and O
WordPress B-SKILL
and O
Ahrefs B-SKILL

ANASTASIIA B-PER
POPOVA I-PER
graduated O
from O
National B-ORG
University I-ORG
'Chernihiv I-ORG
Collegium' I-ORG
named I-ORG
after I-ORG
T. I-ORG
G. I-ORG
Shevchenko I-ORG

Vasyl B-PER
Tusiuk I-PER
is O
a O
Front-end B-PROF
developer I-PROF
based O
in O
Lviv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Egor B-PER
Grigorenko I-PER
from O
Ukraine B-LOC

Android B-PROF
developer I-PROF

Python B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Volodymyr B-PER
Datsiuk I-PER
worked O
as O
Front-end B-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
Softemy B-ORG

Marketing&Sales B-PROF
manager I-PROF

UX/UI B-PROF
Designer I-PROF

Software B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Багина B-PER
Татьяна I-PER
Вадимовна I-PER
worked O
as O
Key B-PROF
Account I-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
VTB B-ORG
Bank I-ORG

Currently O
working O
as O
Senior B-PROF
DevOps I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
Opinov8 B-ORG

Junior B-PROF
DevOps I-PROF

motion B-PROF
designer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
InDesign B-SKILL
and O
Illustrator B-SKILL
and O
Lightroom B-SKILL

SEO B-PROF
специалист I-PROF

Currently O
working O
as O
UX/UI B-PROF
designer, I-PROF
Graphic I-PROF
Designer I-PROF
at O
Bulls B-ORG
Media I-ORG

Iryna B-PER
Pravotorova I-PER
graduated O
from O
V.N. B-ORG
Karazin I-ORG
Kharkiv I-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG

Mykola B-PER
Shulzhenko I-PER
is O
a O
Senior B-PROF
JavaScript I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
based O
in O
USA B-LOC

TROFANYUK B-PER
VLADISLAV I-PER
is O
a O
JUNIOR B-PROF
C# I-PROF
/.NET I-PROF
DEVELOPER I-PROF
based O
in O
Ukraine B-LOC

Sales B-PROF
Manager I-PROF

MARIA B-PER
SANDULIAK I-PER
is O
a O
IT B-PROF
Finance I-PROF
Specialist I-PROF
based O
in O
Kyiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Manual B-PROF
QA I-PROF
Engineer/QA I-PROF
Lead I-PROF

Skills O
: O
Word B-SKILL
Office I-SKILL
, O
Power B-SKILL
Point I-SKILL
, O
Excel B-SKILL

Currently O
working O
as O
Product B-PROF
Marketing I-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
Cprime B-ORG
Studios I-ORG

Bogdan B-PER
Sirenko I-PER

OLEKSII B-PER
SKORUK I-PER

Worked O
at O
Lingoal B-ORG
in O
California, B-LOC
USA I-LOC
May B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
January I-DATE
2019 I-DATE

Krasovskii B-PER
Vladimir I-PER

Studied O
at O
National B-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ukraine I-ORG
“Igor I-ORG
Sikorsky I-ORG
Kyiv I-ORG
Politechnic I-ORG
Institute” I-ORG

Illya B-PER
Shkurko I-PER
worked O
as O
Senior B-PROF
Software I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
Ciklum B-ORG

Full B-PROF
Stack I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Profermer B-ORG
from O
2018.01.01 B-DATE
2018.03.01 I-DATE

Currently O
working O
as O
CUSTOMER B-PROF
CARE I-PROF
REPRESENTATIVE I-PROF
at O
Sahad B-ORG
Stores I-ORG

Worked O
at O
Quality B-ORG
Task I-ORG
Force I-ORG
in O
Hawassa, B-LOC
Ethiopia I-LOC
Jan2019-Aug2021 B-DATE

Experience O
: O
January B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
October I-DATE
2020 I-DATE

Senior|Lead B-PROF
AWS|Heroku I-PROF
& I-PROF
Angular.Js|Angular|Node.Js I-PROF
& I-PROF
JavaScript|TypeScript I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Heroku B-SKILL
and O
Nest.Js B-SKILL
and O
Deno B-SKILL

Front-end B-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
Krivoy B-ORG
Rog I-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG
from O
August B-DATE
2011 I-DATE
August I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

2D B-PROF
artist I-PROF

Ruslana B-PER
Holovata I-PER
is O
a O
Project B-PROF
Manager I-PROF
based O
in O
Lviv B-LOC

Ivan B-PER
Bulka I-PER

Yuliia B-PER
Posypai I-PER
is O
a O
Ux/Ui B-PROF
Designer I-PROF
based O
in O
Dnipro, B-LOC
UA I-LOC

Head B-PROF
of I-PROF
Marketing I-PROF

Investment B-PROF
Analyst I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Creation B-SKILL
of I-SKILL
business I-SKILL
process I-SKILL
diagrams I-SKILL
and O
Writing B-SKILL
test I-SKILL
documentation I-SKILL
and O
API B-SKILL
testing I-SKILL

Front-End B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Worked O
at O
EPAM B-ORG
SYSTEMS I-ORG
in O
Remote B-LOC
11/2020 B-DATE
01/2022 I-DATE

Archil B-PER
Abuladze I-PER
from O
Wrocław, B-LOC
Dolnośląskie, I-LOC
Poland I-LOC

Skills O
: O
Kendo B-SKILL
UI I-SKILL
, O
Angular B-SKILL
, O
MongoDB B-SKILL
, O
RXJS B-SKILL
, O
NPM B-SKILL

Dmitry B-PER
Makaryev I-PER
from O
Odessa B-LOC

Studied O
at O
Academician B-ORG
Y. I-ORG
Bugay I-ORG
International I-ORG
Scientific I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University I-ORG

Experience O
: O
January B-DATE
2012 I-DATE
May I-DATE
2018 I-DATE

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Sass B-SKILL
, O
Figma B-SKILL
, O
Photoshop B-SKILL
, O
VS B-SKILL
Code I-SKILL

Quality B-PROF
Control I-PROF
Manager I-PROF

АЛЕКСАНДР B-PER

Experience O
: O
January B-DATE
2015 I-DATE
July I-DATE
2017 I-DATE

Denys B-PER
Karpov I-PER
worked O
as O
Junior B-PROF
QA I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
TSUM B-ORG
Kyiv I-ORG

ANDREY B-PER
KHOLYAVKA I-PER
worked O
as O
Junior B-PROF
Java I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
GlobalLogic B-ORG

Currently O
working O
as O
Front-End B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Sponge B-ORG
D&D I-ORG

Fredrick B-PER
Otieno I-PER
Oluoch I-PER

Experience O
: O
January- B-DATE
March I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Currently O
working O
as O
IT B-PROF
Project I-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
Itera B-ORG
company I-ORG

Project B-PROF
manager I-PROF

System B-PROF
Specialist I-PROF

Bohdan B-PER
Kryvyi I-PER

PAVLO B-PER
SUKHONOS I-PER
graduated O
from O
State B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Telecommunications I-ORG

Tahir B-PER
Artikov I-PER
from O
Urganch, B-LOC
Xorazm, I-LOC
Uzbekistan I-LOC

Skills O
: O
MySQL B-SKILL
, O
Postman B-SKILL
, O
STLC B-SKILL
, O
mobile B-SKILL
applications I-SKILL
testing I-SKILL
, O
test B-SKILL
design I-SKILL
techniques I-SKILL

Senior B-PROF
Software I-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Formik B-SKILL
, O
firebase B-SKILL
, O
mongodb B-SKILL
, O
react-router-dom B-SKILL

Experience O
: O
Oct B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
Present I-DATE

Studied O
at O
Georgia B-ORG
Tech I-ORG

ANASTASIIA B-PER
SHEVCHUK I-PER

Worked O
at O
Interlogistic B-ORG
in O
Kharkiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC
05/2022 B-DATE
now I-DATE

Artur B-PER
Sydorenko I-PER
from O
USA B-LOC

Software B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Google B-SKILL
Cloud I-SKILL
Platform I-SKILL
and O
Django B-SKILL
and O
JS B-SKILL

Python B-PROF
developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
HTML B-SKILL
and O
Gino B-SKILL
and O
Heroku B-SKILL

Worked O
at O
FinAdviser B-ORG
in O
Ukraine B-LOC
08.2011 B-DATE
04.2012 I-DATE

Denys B-PER
Reshetnykov I-PER
graduated O
from O
National B-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ukraine I-ORG
'Kyiv I-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG
Institute' I-ORG

Oleg B-PER
Shepel I-PER
from O
Ukraine B-LOC

Currently O
working O
as O
Junior B-PROF
Android I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Parimatch B-ORG
tech I-ORG

NIGAR B-PER
ALIZADA I-PER
worked O
as O
Data B-PROF
base I-PROF
administrator I-PROF
at O
KAPITAL B-ORG
BANK I-ORG
OJSC I-ORG

.NET B-PROF
Trainee I-PROF

Tahir B-PER
Yagubov I-PER
from O
Baku, B-LOC
Azerbaijan I-LOC

Experience O
: O
December B-DATE
2010 I-DATE
April I-DATE
2015 I-DATE

АНДРІЙ B-PER
ОЛЕКСІЄНКО I-PER
from O
м. B-LOC
Кам’янське I-LOC

ALINA B-PER
KROT I-PER
from O
ZAPORIZHZHYA B-LOC

Skills O
: O
LiveDune B-SKILL
, O
Figma B-SKILL
, O
Jira B-SKILL
, O
SWOT B-SKILL
and I-SKILL
Competitor I-SKILL
Analysis I-SKILL
, O
Video B-SKILL
editing I-SKILL
for I-SKILL
Instagram I-SKILL

Currently O
working O
as O
UI/UX B-PROF
designer I-PROF
at O
PBRIT B-ORG
& I-ORG
ZMLA I-ORG

Technical O
expertise O
: O
git B-SKILL
, O
Jira B-SKILL
, O
JavaScript B-SKILL
Algorithms I-SKILL
and I-SKILL
Data I-SKILL
Structures I-SKILL
, O
TypeScript B-SKILL

PHP B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Roman B-PER
Sliuz I-PER

Studied O
at O
Kyiv B-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG
Institute I-ORG

Project B-PROF
coordinator I-PROF

Yasin B-PER
Mehdiyev I-PER
graduated O
from O
Bachelor's B-ORG
degree, I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science I-ORG
ASOIU(Azerbaijan I-ORG
State I-ORG
Oil I-ORG
and I-ORG
Industry I-ORG
University) I-ORG

Studied O
at O
IT B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
Hebron I-ORG
Academy I-ORG

Worked O
at O
UserWay B-ORG
in O
Kyiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC
11/2021 B-DATE
present I-DATE

Full B-PROF
Stack I-PROF
Blockchain I-PROF
Development I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
JavaScript B-SKILL
Frameworks I-SKILL
and O
Artificial B-SKILL
Intelligence I-SKILL
(AI) I-SKILL
and O
Design B-SKILL

Igor B-PER
Marin I-PER
is O
a O
Project B-PROF
manager I-PROF
based O
in O
Kiev, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Software B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
(Contract) I-PROF
at O
Fainzy B-ORG
Technologies I-ORG
from O
February B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
April I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Ivan B-PER
Rozinko I-PER

Ecommerce B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
& I-PROF
Project I-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
GetApp B-ORG
Group I-ORG
from O
Jan B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
Mar I-DATE
2023 I-DATE

Ilya B-PER
Zinckevich I-PER
worked O
as O
Data B-PROF
Scientist I-PROF
at O
ITSvit B-ORG

Currently O
working O
as O
Software B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
The B-ORG
Tateeda I-ORG
Incorporation I-ORG

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Docker B-SKILL
, O
Vue.js B-SKILL
, O
Linux B-SKILL
, O
English B-SKILL
intermediate I-SKILL

Harutyun B-PER
Hovakimyan I-PER
Ph.D. I-PER

JOSEPH B-PER
AYOBAMI I-PER
worked O
as O
Software B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
Zercom B-ORG
Systems I-ORG
from O
July B-DATE
2015 I-DATE
July I-DATE
2017 I-DATE

network B-PROF
admin I-PROF

Skills O
: O
Team B-SKILL
Leadership I-SKILL
, O
People B-SKILL
Management I-SKILL
, O
Project B-SKILL
Management I-SKILL
, O
Process B-SKILL
management I-SKILL
, O
Stakeholder B-SKILL
Management I-SKILL

Software B-PROF
React I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
TypeScript B-SKILL
and O
React B-SKILL
Testing I-SKILL
Library I-SKILL
and O
Sass/Less B-SKILL

Technical O
expertise O
: O
HTML B-SKILL
, O
XML B-SKILL
, O
SQL B-SKILL
, O
Blockchain B-SKILL

System B-PROF
Support I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF

UX/UI B-PROF
Designer I-PROF
at O
Freelance B-ORG
from O
Jul B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
Jul I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Software B-PROF
Tester I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Git B-SKILL
and O
Github B-SKILL
and O
SQL B-SKILL
basics I-SKILL

Amazon B-PROF
Entrepreneur I-PROF

Khasay B-PER
Mirzali I-PER

Currently O
working O
as O
Frontend B-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
Web B-ORG
studio I-ORG
Byshep I-ORG

Head B-PROF
Of I-PROF
SEO I-PROF

SULTAN B-PER
ISRAFILZADE I-PER
is O
a O
INDUSTRIAL B-PROF
AND I-PROF
PLANNING I-PROF
ENGINEER I-PROF
based O
in O
REMOTE B-LOC
UKRAINE I-LOC

Head B-PROF
of I-PROF
Digital I-PROF

Freelance B-PROF
at O
1+1 B-ORG
media I-ORG
from O
07/2021 B-DATE

Technical O
expertise O
: O
PHP B-SKILL
, O
Git B-SKILL
, O
React B-SKILL
Native I-SKILL
, O
React B-SKILL

Yidnekachew B-PER
(Yidne) I-PER
Tafese I-PER
from O
London, B-LOC
UK I-LOC

Worked O
at O
PROKON B-ORG
in O
REMOTE B-LOC
RUSSIA I-LOC
08/2022 B-DATE
Present I-DATE

Vadym B-PER
Fedorenko I-PER
worked O
as O
Software B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Darin B-ORG
X I-ORG

Project B-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
YayPay, B-ORG
Inc I-ORG
from O
May B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
May I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Dasha B-PER
Kobylynska I-PER

Studied O
at O
Bachelors B-ORG
of I-ORG
Marketing I-ORG

Experience O
: O
MARCH B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
APRIL I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Software B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
Deem B-ORG
Incorporation I-ORG
from O
February B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
June I-DATE
2019 I-DATE

UI/UX B-PROF
Design I-PROF
Assistant I-PROF

Business B-PROF
analyst I-PROF

Anduamlak B-PER
Berhanu I-PER
graduated O
from O
HiLCoE B-ORG
School I-ORG
of I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Science I-ORG
and I-ORG
Technology I-ORG

Web B-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
ConceptArea B-ORG
from O
04/2018 B-DATE
07/2020 I-DATE

Worked O
at O
Trendo B-ORG
in O
Odessa B-LOC
OCTOBER B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
APRIL I-DATE
2020 I-DATE

Natalia B-PER
Shutenko I-PER
worked O
as O
Junior B-PROF
frontend I-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
DiJust B-ORG

Junior B-PROF
Software I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF

Illya B-PER
Shkurko I-PER
graduated O
from O
State B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Telecommunications I-ORG

Studied O
at O
Ivan B-ORG
Franko I-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Lviv I-ORG

Studied O
at O
V.N. B-ORG
Karazina I-ORG
Kharkiv I-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG
School I-ORG
of I-ORG
Radiophysics, I-ORG
Biomedical I-ORG
Electronics I-ORG
and I-ORG
Computer I-ORG
Systems I-ORG

Golang B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Web B-ORG
Design I-ORG
Sun I-ORG
from O
сен B-DATE
2015 I-DATE
мар I-DATE
2016 I-DATE

Dmytro B-PER
Shevchenko I-PER
graduated O
from O
Donetsk B-ORG
National I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University I-ORG

Senior B-PROF
Quality I-PROF
Assurance I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF

Vitaliy B-PER
Tyshkov I-PER

Applications B-PROF
& I-PROF
Integration I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Active B-SKILL
Directory I-SKILL
and O
Git B-SKILL
and O
Confluence B-SKILL

Mykyta B-PER
Yunoshev I-PER
graduated O
from O
Kharkiv B-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Radioelectronics I-ORG

HABTU B-PER
LEGESSE I-PER
worked O
as O
Lead B-PROF
Back-End I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Perago B-ORG
Information I-ORG
Systems I-ORG

Denys B-PER
Reshetnykov I-PER
worked O
as O
Senior B-PROF
Technical I-PROF
Product I-PROF
Expert I-PROF
at O
Playtika B-ORG
from O
мая B-DATE
2010 I-DATE
апреля I-DATE
2011 I-DATE

Back-End B-PROF
developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
SQS B-SKILL
and O
AWS(APIGateway) B-SKILL
and O
Vue2(Vuex) B-SKILL

HR B-PROF
Manager/Recruiter I-PROF
at O
Netframe B-ORG
from O
Jun. B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
Feb. I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Currently O
working O
as O
PRODUCT B-PROF
SUPPORT I-PROF
INTERN I-PROF
at O
KHAN B-ORG
ACADEMY I-ORG
AZERBAIJANI I-ORG

Skills O
: O
Issue B-SKILL
Tracking I-SKILL
System I-SKILL
(Mantis) I-SKILL
, O
HTTP B-SKILL
, O
Postman B-SKILL
, O
Software B-SKILL
Testing I-SKILL
, O
HTML/CSS B-SKILL

Frontend B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Weather B-ORG
App I-ORG
from O
Oct. B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Ongoing I-DATE

Web B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Currently O
working O
as O
Software B-PROF
engineer I-PROF
at O
KP B-ORG
VTI I-ORG

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Kafka B-SKILL
, O
Redis B-SKILL
, O
NodeJS/Express B-SKILL
, O
SQL B-SKILL

Studied O
at O
National B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Tarasa I-ORG
Shevchenka I-ORG

Worked O
at O
eKreative B-ORG
in O
Lviv B-LOC
08/2021 B-DATE
Present I-DATE

Software B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
(Contract) I-PROF

Studied O
at O
V. B-ORG
N. I-ORG
Karazin I-ORG
Kharkiv I-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG

Front-end B-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
Softemy B-ORG
from O
November B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
Present I-DATE

Egor B-PER
Vakulenko I-PER
graduated O
from O
Kyiv B-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Construction I-ORG
and I-ORG
Architect I-ORG

Kidanemariam B-PER
Argaw I-PER

Team B-PROF
Lead I-PROF
of I-PROF
Community I-PROF
Managers I-PROF

DMYTRO B-PER
GRYGORASH I-PER
is O
a O
Frontend B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
based O
in O
Kyiv B-LOC

Software B-PROF
development I-PROF
(Web I-PROF
design) I-PROF
at O
Swapmoney B-ORG
from O
May, B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Present I-DATE

SOFTWARE B-PROF
ENGINNER I-PROF

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Angular B-SKILL
2+ I-SKILL
, O
LESS B-SKILL
, O
InVision B-SKILL
, O
Zeplin B-SKILL

Kozenko B-PER
Serhii I-PER
graduated O
from O
National B-ORG
Transport I-ORG
University I-ORG

Mark B-PER
Velichkovskiy I-PER

Studied O
at O
Azerbaijan B-ORG
State I-ORG
Economic I-ORG
University I-ORG

ELMADDI B-PER
N I-PER
ALI I-PER
YEV I-PER
worked O
as O
Data B-PROF
Analyst I-PROF
at O
Veyseloglu B-ORG
Group I-ORG
of I-ORG
Companies I-ORG

Skills O
: O
Confluence B-SKILL
, O
AWS B-SKILL
, O
Slack B-SKILL
, O
CI/CD B-SKILL
, O
SDLC B-SKILL

Studied O
at O
Киевский B-ORG
национальный I-ORG
университет I-ORG
культуры I-ORG
и I-ORG
искусств I-ORG

Experience O
: O
Jan B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
Aug I-DATE
2020 I-DATE

БОГДАН B-PER
МОРОЗЮК I-PER

Daniil B-PER
Selivanov I-PER
graduated O
from O
Kyiv B-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Taras I-ORG
Shevchenko I-ORG

Currently O
working O
as O
Customer B-PROF
Support I-PROF
Manager, I-PROF
Operations I-PROF
at O
Klal B-ORG
Insurance I-ORG

Dmytro B-PER
Mandryka I-PER

Anastasiia B-PER
Kinova I-PER
worked O
as O
SENIOR B-PROF
CONTENT I-PROF
MANAGER I-PROF
at O
CLEVERR B-ORG

Rostyk B-PER
Biletskyy I-PER

Vue B-PROF
js I-PROF
разработчик I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
React B-SKILL
and O
Mongo B-SKILL
DB I-SKILL
and O
Nuxt B-SKILL
js I-SKILL

Fraol B-PER
Kumera I-PER
from O
Addis B-LOC
Ababa, I-LOC
Ethiopia I-LOC

Skills O
: O
CSS B-SKILL
, O
Entity B-SKILL
framework I-SKILL
, O
Xamarin.Forms B-SKILL
, O
C#/.Net B-SKILL
, O
ADO.NET B-SKILL

Currently O
working O
as O
Content B-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
Koala B-ORG
Masters I-ORG

Skills O
: O
Mocha B-SKILL
, O
SOLID B-SKILL
, O
Redux B-SKILL
, O
APEX B-SKILL
, O
Chai B-SKILL

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Troubleshooting B-SKILL
, O
Teamwork B-SKILL
, O
Customer B-SKILL
service I-SKILL
, O
Decision-making B-SKILL

Kateryna B-PER
Krolevetska I-PER
worked O
as O
Middle B-PROF
QA I-PROF
(Manual) I-PROF
at O
Grid B-ORG
Dynamics I-ORG

Experience O
: O
Aug, B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
present I-DATE

Software B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
GO B-SKILL
and O
Hibernate B-SKILL
and O
Redis B-SKILL

Skills O
: O
Analytical B-SKILL
thinking I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft B-SKILL
Office I-SKILL
, O
Upper-Intermediate B-SKILL
English I-SKILL

Vitaliy B-PER
Tyshkov I-PER
from O
Rivne, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Worked O
at O
CyberBionic B-ORG
Systematics I-ORG
in O
Kyiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC
Nov.2022–Now B-DATE

RASHAD B-PER
AKHUNDOV I-PER
from O
Baku B-LOC

Ruslan B-PER
Erzhanov I-PER

Skills O
: O
Sockets B-SKILL
, O
OneSignal B-SKILL
, O
Versioning B-SKILL
control I-SKILL
system I-SKILL
, O
Autolayout B-SKILL
, O
AVFoundtaion B-SKILL

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Maven B-SKILL
, O
Groovy B-SKILL
, O
English B-SKILL
Upper-Intermediate I-SKILL
, O
SQL(PostgreSQL, B-SKILL
SQL I-SKILL
Server) I-SKILL

Aleksandr B-PER
Oleshko I-PER

ANATOLII B-PER
LITYNSKYI I-PER

Senior B-PROF
.Net I-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Nihad B-PER
Abbasov I-PER
graduated O
from O
International B-ORG
Bank I-ORG
of I-ORG
Azerbaijan I-ORG

Currently O
working O
as O
Frontend B-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
Codevog B-ORG

CONTRACT B-PROF
BUSINESS I-PROF
ANALYST I-PROF
TECHNICAL I-PROF
WRITER I-PROF

Business B-PROF
analyst I-PROF

Projects B-PROF
Manager I-PROF
Implementation I-PROF

HTML-coder B-PROF
at O
Software B-ORG
Smart I-ORG
Solutions I-ORG
from O
09.2015 B-DATE
Present I-DATE

Inna B-PER
Chubko I-PER
worked O
as O
Patrol B-PROF
Police I-PROF
Officer I-PROF
at O
National B-ORG
Police I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ukraine I-ORG

SOFTWARE B-PROF
ENGINEER I-PROF
at O
KIBRIT B-ORG
from O
SEP B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
PRESENT I-DATE

Experience O
: O
July B-DATE
2016 I-DATE
August I-DATE
2017 I-DATE

Android B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
MVP B-SKILL
and O
GraphQL B-SKILL
and O
Git B-SKILL

Technical O
expertise O
: O
React/Redux B-SKILL
, O
React B-SKILL
, O
npm B-SKILL
, O
Redux B-SKILL

Java B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Senior B-PROF
QA I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF

Saba B-PER
Khais I-PER
worked O
as O
Project B-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
Amit B-ORG
Global I-ORG
from O
April B-DATE
2007 I-DATE
to I-DATE
April I-DATE
2008 I-DATE

Oleg B-PER
Gardash I-PER
from O
Kyiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Software B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF

Studied O
at O
National B-ORG
Aviation I-ORG
University I-ORG

Experience O
: O
March B-DATE
2014 I-DATE
August I-DATE
2019 I-DATE

Full B-PROF
Stack I-PROF
Blockchain I-PROF
Development I-PROF

Vitaliy B-PER
Tyshkov I-PER
graduated O
from O
International B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Economics I-ORG
and I-ORG
Humanities I-ORG

Yehor B-PER
Azyrankulov I-PER
worked O
as O
Part-time B-PROF
Front I-PROF
end I-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
ISS B-ORG
from O
06/2021 B-DATE
09/2021 I-DATE

Studied O
at O
Ukrainian B-ORG
Catholic I-ORG
University I-ORG

Anton B-PER
Smirnov I-PER

Experience O
: O
July B-DATE
2021-February I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Currently O
working O
as O
Sales B-PROF
manager I-PROF
at O
NOVBUD B-ORG

Senior B-PROF
Back I-PROF
End I-PROF
Cloud I-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Technical O
expertise O
: O
API B-SKILL
testing I-SKILL
basics I-SKILL
, O
SQL B-SKILL
basics I-SKILL
, O
Manual B-SKILL
QA I-SKILL
, O
Web/Desktop/Mobile B-SKILL
testing I-SKILL

Vadym B-PER
Hemba I-PER
from O
Ukraine B-LOC

Studied O
at O
The B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Tokyo I-ORG

Technical O
expertise O
: O
PHP B-SKILL
, O
Unix B-SKILL
, O
JQuery B-SKILL
, O
CSS3 B-SKILL

Studied O
at O
Infopulse B-ORG
Univer I-ORG

Vehicle B-PROF
3D I-PROF
artist I-PROF

Front-end B-PROF
developer I-PROF

Business B-PROF
Development I-PROF
Manager I-PROF

Skills O
: O
3d B-SKILL
coat I-SKILL
, O
Rizomuv B-SKILL
, O
Maya B-SKILL
, O
human B-SKILL
anatomy I-SKILL
, O
Zbrush B-SKILL

Currently O
working O
as O
Junior B-PROF
to I-PROF
Senior I-PROF
Java I-PROF
developer I-PROF
and I-PROF
Big I-PROF
Data I-PROF
engineer I-PROF
at O
Luxoft B-ORG

Worked O
at O
Brand B-ORG
Father I-ORG
in O
Kyiv B-LOC
03/2019 B-DATE
06/2019 I-DATE

PAVLOVSKA B-PER
NATA I-PER
worked O
as O
WEB B-PROF
/ I-PROF
GRAPHIC I-PROF
DESIGNER I-PROF
/ I-PROF
PROJECT I-PROF
MANAGER I-PROF
at O
Develium B-ORG
web I-ORG
agency I-ORG

Co-founder B-PROF
at O
ALF B-ORG
Real I-ORG
Estate I-ORG
Company I-ORG
from O
сентября B-DATE
2004 I-DATE
февраля I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Windows B-SKILL
, O
Test B-SKILL
Documentation I-SKILL
, O
HTML B-SKILL
, O
Github B-SKILL

DANA B-PER
DOVZHENKO I-PER
graduated O
from O
National B-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ukraine I-ORG
“Igor I-ORG
Sikorsky I-ORG
Kyiv I-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG
Institute” I-ORG

Bayduzh B-PER
Oleksandr I-PER
worked O
as O
Technical B-PROF
support I-PROF
specialist I-PROF
at O
Servers.com B-ORG
from O
10.2021 B-DATE
until I-DATE
01.2022 I-DATE

Experience O
: O
07/2018 B-DATE
03/2019 I-DATE

Tester B-PROF

Tetiana B-PER
Handziur I-PER
graduated O
from O
Projector B-ORG
Creative I-ORG
& I-ORG
Tech I-ORG
Online I-ORG
Institute I-ORG

Skills O
: O
Spock B-SKILL
framework I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft B-SKILL
SQL I-SKILL
Server I-SKILL
, O
Hibernate B-SKILL
, O
Spring B-SKILL
Data I-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL B-SKILL

Intermediate B-PROF
UX/UI I-PROF
Designer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Express.js B-SKILL
and O
Node B-SKILL
JS I-SKILL
and O
C# B-SKILL

Valeriia B-PER
Honcharuck I-PER
worked O
as O
Graphic B-PROF
designer I-PROF
at O
Arena B-ORG
CS I-ORG
from O
March B-DATE
2016 I-DATE
September I-DATE
2018 I-DATE

Worked O
at O
Zamzam, B-ORG
first I-ORG
fair I-ORG
digital I-ORG
bank I-ORG
in O
Kropyvnytskyi B-LOC
2020 B-DATE
CURRENT I-DATE

Skills O
: O
Scrum B-SKILL
methodology I-SKILL
, O
web B-SKILL
and I-SKILL
mobile I-SKILL
applications I-SKILL
, O
test B-SKILL
cases I-SKILL
writing I-SKILL
, O
AppCenter B-SKILL
, O
web B-SKILL
testing I-SKILL

Front B-PROF
End I-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Worked O
at O
Craft B-ORG
Software I-ORG
Professionals I-ORG
in O
Addis B-LOC
Ababa, I-LOC
Ethiopia I-LOC
07/2022 B-DATE
to I-DATE
current I-DATE

Sofiia B-PER
Mikadze I-PER
worked O
as O
Data B-PROF
Analyst I-PROF
& I-PROF
Sales I-PROF
Intern I-PROF
at O
NXP B-ORG
Semiconductors I-ORG

Studied O
at O
National B-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ukraine I-ORG
'Kiev I-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG
Institute' I-ORG
(NTUU I-ORG
'KPI') I-ORG

Studied O
at O
Mechenical-Metalorgical B-ORG
technical I-ORG
school I-ORG

Skills O
: O
HTML B-SKILL
, O
Jwt B-SKILL
, O
React B-SKILL
, O
SCSS B-SKILL
, O
JavaScript B-SKILL

Vadym B-PER
Diachenko I-PER
graduated O
from O
Vinnytsia B-ORG
National I-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University I-ORG

Skills O
: O
Google B-SKILL
Analytics I-SKILL
, O
Figma B-SKILL
, O
HTML/CSS B-SKILL
, O
HotJar B-SKILL
, O
WordPress B-SKILL

Skills O
: O
Coroutines B-SKILL
, O
Firebase B-SKILL
Crashlytics I-SKILL
, O
Android B-SKILL
AppMetrica I-SKILL
, O
HTML B-SKILL
, O
Glide B-SKILL

React B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Skills O
: O
Project B-SKILL
Management I-SKILL
, O
E-Commerce B-SKILL
, O
JavaScript B-SKILL
Frameworks I-SKILL
, O
Client B-SKILL
Relations I-SKILL
, O
PHP B-SKILL
Frameworks I-SKILL

Skills O
: O
SQL B-SKILL
Server I-SKILL
, O
High B-SKILL
chart I-SKILL
, O
Azure B-SKILL
Cosmos I-SKILL
, O
HTML5 B-SKILL
, O
Oracle B-SKILL

Worked O
at O
Info-Region B-ORG
in O
Freelancehunt B-LOC
03/2021 B-DATE
11/2021 I-DATE

Ali B-PER
Suleymanlı I-PER
worked O
as O
Responsible B-PROF
for I-PROF
planning I-PROF
of I-PROF
the I-PROF
manufacturing I-PROF
processes I-PROF
at O
Modenis B-ORG
LLC I-ORG

Junior B-PROF
DevOps I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF

Mostafa B-PER
Mahmoud I-PER
Hashem I-PER
is O
a O
Unity B-PROF
developer I-PROF
based O
in O
Cairo B-LOC

Skills O
: O
CSS B-SKILL
, O
HTML B-SKILL
, O
Figma B-SKILL

Fullstack B-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
Temy B-ORG
from O
05.2022 B-DATE
present I-DATE

Experience O
: O
Apr B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Present I-DATE

Trainee/Intern/Junior B-PROF
QA I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
(Automation) I-PROF

Valeryi B-PER
Pyskun I-PER
graduated O
from O
Dnipropetrovsk B-ORG
National I-ORG
university I-ORG

Ksyonz B-PER
David I-PER
worked O
as O
QA B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
DTEK B-ORG
from O
6 B-DATE
month I-DATE

Serhii B-PER
Hennadiiovych I-PER
Kyzym I-PER
worked O
as O
QA B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
DMD B-ORG
Binary I-ORG

Bayduzh B-PER
Oleksandr I-PER
is O
a O
Maintenance B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
based O
in O
K3-Soft, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Django B-SKILL
REST I-SKILL
Framework I-SKILL
, O
Python B-SKILL
, O
Django B-SKILL
, O
Typescript B-SKILL

Igor B-PER
Shulgin I-PER
worked O
as O
Tech B-PROF
Lead I-PROF
at O
IRST B-ORG
Ukraine I-ORG

Viktor B-PER
Burenin I-PER
is O
a O
Brand B-PROF
Representative I-PROF
based O
in O
WooW B-LOC
Canada I-LOC

Tony B-PER
(Katsu) I-PER
Dai I-PER
is O
a O
Full B-PROF
Stack I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
based O
in O
CANNAVIGIA B-LOC

PROJECT B-PROF
MANAGEMENT I-PROF
CONSULTANT I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
SCRUM B-SKILL
and O
Waterfall B-SKILL
and I-SKILL
Agile I-SKILL
Project I-SKILL
Management I-SKILL
and O
Consulting B-SKILL

Currently O
working O
as O
GIS B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Excellerent B-ORG
Solutions I-ORG

Skills O
: O
Copywriting B-SKILL
, O
Languages B-SKILL
, O
UI/UX B-SKILL
design I-SKILL

Worked O
at O
StarApps B-ORG
in O
Lviv B-LOC
Oct B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
Apr I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Olga B-PER
Hutsuluk I-PER
worked O
as O
Economist B-PROF
-accountant I-PROF
at O
IT B-ORG
School I-ORG
GoIT I-ORG

Vusiker B-PER
Oleg I-PER
from O
Dnepropetrovsk B-LOC

Sourcer B-PROF

Studied O
at O
National B-ORG
Technical I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ukraine I-ORG
“Igor I-ORG
Sikorsky I-ORG
Kyiv I-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG
Institute” I-ORG

Denys B-PER
Konoval I-PER
worked O
as O
Frontend B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
ActiveWizards B-ORG
from O
11/2016 B-DATE
03/2018 I-DATE

Ірина B-PER
Другашова I-PER

Skills O
: O
SEO B-SKILL
, O
SMM B-SKILL
, O
JavaScript B-SKILL
, O
Jira B-SKILL
, O
Waterfall B-SKILL

PAVLO B-PER
SUKHONOS I-PER
from O
Kyiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Figma B-SKILL
, O
MVVM B-SKILL
, O
Foundation B-SKILL
, O
Git B-SKILL

Fillip B-PER
Lungu I-PER
is O
a O
Senior B-PROF
Designer I-PROF
based O
in O
Ukraine B-LOC

QA B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
HTML B-SKILL
and O
SQL B-SKILL
and O
Confluence B-SKILL

Currently O
working O
as O
Middle B-PROF
React I-PROF
Front I-PROF
End I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Mediasapiens B-ORG
Gmbh I-ORG

Skills O
: O
Python B-SKILL
, O
Docs B-SKILL
API I-SKILL
, O
Google B-SKILL
Cloud I-SKILL
Platform I-SKILL
, O
Drive B-SKILL
API I-SKILL
, O
React B-SKILL

Anton B-PER
Bohdan I-PER

Tetiana B-PER
Gordynska I-PER
graduated O
from O
School B-ORG
№99, I-ORG
Lviv I-ORG

Konstantin B-PER
Stupen' I-PER

Victor B-PER
Onyshko I-PER
worked O
as O
Software B-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
Abbott B-ORG
from O
1 B-DATE
year I-DATE

Rostyslav B-PER
Malaniuk I-PER

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Ubuntu B-SKILL
, O
Python/Bash B-SKILL
, O
2008R2/2012/2012R2/2016 B-SKILL
, O
Consul B-SKILL

Olga B-PER
Hutsuluk I-PER

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Photoshop B-SKILL
, O
testing B-SKILL
documentation I-SKILL
, O
SQL B-SKILL
, O
consulting B-SKILL
for I-SKILL
users I-SKILL

Currently O
working O
as O
Fullstack B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
JetSoftPro B-ORG
LLC I-ORG

Junior B-PROF
Angular I-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Maxim B-PER
Dyn I-PER
is O
a O
PHP B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
based O
in O
Vedius B-LOC
Soft I-LOC
s.r.o. I-LOC

Studied O
at O
Kyiv B-ORG
polytechnic I-ORG
institute I-ORG
(KPI) I-ORG

VICTOR B-PER
SVISTUNOV I-PER
worked O
as O
Product B-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
Braf.Tech B-ORG

Worked O
at O
Global B-ORG
Village I-ORG
in O
CIS B-LOC
2019 B-DATE

Alex B-PER
Reznichenko I-PER
from O
Kropyvnytskyi B-LOC

Anna B-PER
Vorobiova I-PER
worked O
as O
Project B-PROF
manager/ I-PROF
business I-PROF
analyst I-PROF
at O
airSlate B-ORG
from O
09/2019 B-DATE
09/2021 I-DATE

Engine B-PROF
Programmer I-PROF
Senior I-PROF
Engine I-PROF
Programmer I-PROF

Irina B-PER
Breza I-PER
graduated O
from O
Udemy B-ORG

Senior B-PROF
Operations I-PROF
Program I-PROF
Manager I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Decision-making B-SKILL
and O
Global B-SKILL
business I-SKILL
operations I-SKILL
skills I-SKILL
and O
Analytical B-SKILL
and I-SKILL
Critical I-SKILL
Thinking I-SKILL

Skills O
: O
HAML B-SKILL
, O
SCSS B-SKILL
, O
VueJS B-SKILL
, O
Git B-SKILL
, O
XSLT B-SKILL

Unity3D B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Alurum B-ORG
from O
January B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
July I-DATE
2019 I-DATE

Stanislav B-PER
Kirkilevsky I-PER
worked O
as O
Painter B-PROF
/ I-PROF
2D I-PROF
Artist I-PROF
at O
Freelance B-ORG
from O
2015-2022 B-DATE

Pavlo B-PER
Piliuiko I-PER

Oleh B-PER
Skrypets I-PER
graduated O
from O
Academy B-ORG
of I-ORG
Customs I-ORG
Economy I-ORG

Serhii B-PER
Liahera I-PER
worked O
as O
JUNIOR B-PROF
PHP I-PROF
DEVELOPER I-PROF
at O
REVISIOR B-ORG

Worked O
at O
Gotoinc B-ORG
in O
Kharkiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC
03.2020 B-DATE
Present I-DATE

UGUR B-PER
CETIN I-PER

PHP B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
PROFI B-ORG
from O
01/2016 B-DATE
05/2017 I-DATE

Junior B-PROF
.NET I-PROF
+ I-PROF
Angular I-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
EPAM B-ORG
from O
April B-DATE
2021 I-DATE
April I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

Popov B-PER
Maxim I-PER

Skills O
: O
Strategic B-SKILL
Planning I-SKILL
, O
Agile B-SKILL
methodologies I-SKILL
, O
TOC B-SKILL
, O
Theory B-SKILL
of I-SKILL
Constraints I-SKILL
, O
Project B-SKILL
Planning I-SKILL

Currently O
working O
as O
Product B-PROF
Manager I-PROF
at O
Blockchain B-ORG
project I-ORG

Aleksandr B-PER
Serdiuk I-PER
is O
a O
QA B-PROF
manual I-PROF
engineer I-PROF
based O
in O
Kyiv B-LOC

Lead B-PROF
Front-end I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF

Skills O
: O
ES6+ B-SKILL
, O
Next.js B-SKILL
, O
GraphQL B-SKILL
, O
Redux B-SKILL
, O
CSS3 B-SKILL

Lead B-PROF
Generation I-PROF
Manager I-PROF

Natali B-PER
Krymskaya I-PER
is O
a O
Technical B-PROF
Project I-PROF
Manager I-PROF
(Senior) I-PROF
based O
in O
Ukraine B-LOC

Currently O
working O
as O
Full B-PROF
Stack I-PROF
Web I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Promodex B-ORG

Nazar B-PER
Kravets I-PER
is O
a O
Methodologist B-PROF
based O
in O
Ukraine B-LOC

Team B-PROF
lead I-PROF

OLHA B-PER
SKULSKA I-PER
graduated O
from O
National B-ORG
Academy I-ORG
of I-ORG
Internal I-ORG
Affairs I-ORG

Project B-PROF
manager I-PROF

Sviatoslav B-PER
worked O
as O
Front-end B-PROF
(HTML/CSS/JS/Wordpress) I-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
PineDev B-ORG
Studio I-ORG

Sofya B-PER
Horokhova I-PER

PHILIP B-PER
KLISHCHOV I-PER
worked O
as O
Marketing B-PROF
team I-PROF
lead I-PROF
at O
NDA B-ORG

Skills O
: O
Node.js B-SKILL
, O
Visual B-SKILL
Studio I-SKILL
Code I-SKILL
, O
Chrome B-SKILL
DevTools I-SKILL
, O
Sublime B-SKILL
text I-SKILL
3 I-SKILL
, O
Pascal B-SKILL

Ivan B-PER
Voloboyev I-PER
graduated O
from O
National B-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Kyiv-Mohyla I-ORG
Academy I-ORG

Kamil B-PER
Muradzade I-PER
graduated O
from O
Baku B-ORG
State I-ORG
University I-ORG

Product B-PROF
designer I-PROF

Skills O
: O
Docker B-SKILL
, O
clean B-SKILL
code I-SKILL
, O
ELKstack B-SKILL
, O
REST B-SKILL
API I-SKILL
, O
DRY B-SKILL

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Smartsheet B-SKILL
, O
Miro B-SKILL
, O
Google B-SKILL
Docs I-SKILL
, O
Project B-SKILL
Charter I-SKILL

UI/UX B-PROF

JUNIOR B-PROF
PHP I-PROF
DEVELOPER I-PROF

Ux/Ui B-PROF
Designer I-PROF
at O
Vreal B-ORG
Soft I-ORG
from O
July B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
October I-DATE
2022 I-DATE

ARTEM B-PER
HURSKYI I-PER
worked O
as O
Quality B-PROF
assurance I-PROF
engineer I-PROF
at O
Thunder B-ORG
Soft I-ORG
from O
Apr B-DATE
2022 I-DATE
Present I-DATE

Khasay B-PER
Mirzali I-PER
from O
Budapest, B-LOC
Hungary I-LOC

Mykhaylo B-PER
Ilnytskyy I-PER
worked O
as O
Front-end B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Ukrtelecom B-ORG

Skills O
: O
client B-SKILL
relationship I-SKILL
management I-SKILL
, O
PM B-SKILL
methodologies I-SKILL
(Waterfall, I-SKILL
Agile I-SKILL
Scrum, I-SKILL
Kanban) I-SKILL
, O
risk B-SKILL
management I-SKILL
, O
tenders B-SKILL
conducting I-SKILL
, O
technical B-SKILL
tasks I-SKILL
preparation I-SKILL

Project B-PROF
Manager I-PROF

CATHERINE B-PER
LEVCHENIA I-PER
graduated O
from O
NTUU B-ORG
"KPI" I-ORG

Worked O
at O
SierraGroup B-ORG
in O
UA B-LOC
2011-2016 B-DATE

Worked O
at O
ARTCUBE B-ORG
in O
Kyiv, B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC
Sep B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
Sep I-DATE
2019 I-DATE

Technical O
expertise O
: O
V B-SKILL
model I-SKILL
, O
REST B-SKILL
, O
Kanban B-SKILL
, O
MS B-SKILL
SQL I-SKILL
Server I-SKILL

Unity B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Mykhailo B-PER
Mitiankin I-PER

Sintayehu B-PER
Mengistu I-PER
worked O
as O
ESB/SOFTWARE B-PROF
ENGINEER I-PROF
at O
Exceed B-ORG
IT I-ORG
Systems I-ORG

ANDREY B-PER
KHOLYAVKA I-PER
graduated O
from O
Software B-ORG
Testing I-ORG
Engineer I-ORG

Maksym B-PER
Pasternak I-PER

Ryzhov B-PER
Vitalii I-PER
worked O
as O
C++ B-PROF
Software I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
GlobalLogic B-ORG
from O
October B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
January I-DATE
2019 I-DATE

Lead B-PROF
iOS I-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Web B-PROF
and I-PROF
Mobile I-PROF
application I-PROF
testing I-PROF

Alexander B-PER
Sichinava I-PER
worked O
as O
DIGITAL B-PROF
MARKETING I-PROF
MANAGER I-PROF
at O
Alterway B-ORG
from O
2021-Present B-DATE

Tony B-PER
(Katsu) I-PER
Dai I-PER
worked O
as O
Full B-PROF
Stack I-PROF
Blockchain I-PROF
Development I-PROF
at O
NIPPON B-ORG
EXPRESS I-ORG
GROUP I-ORG
from O
Jan B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
Mar I-DATE
2023 I-DATE

Studied O
at O
Ariel B-ORG
University I-ORG
(Israel) I-ORG

Studied O
at O
Kyiv B-ORG
National I-ORG
University I-ORG
of I-ORG
Culture I-ORG
and I-ORG
Arts I-ORG

Junior B-PROF
Java I-PROF
developer I-PROF

Experience O
: O
Jul B-DATE
2017 I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Hive B-SKILL
, O
Delta B-SKILL
Lakes I-SKILL
, O
HDFS B-SKILL
, O
SSIS B-SKILL

Technical O
expertise O
: O
C# B-SKILL
, O
Postman B-SKILL
, O
load B-SKILL
testing I-SKILL
, O
test B-SKILL
documentation I-SKILL

Sous B-PROF
chef I-PROF

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Figma B-SKILL
, O
Icons B-SKILL
and I-SKILL
Typography I-SKILL
, O
UI B-SKILL
Kit I-SKILL
, O
Interaction B-SKILL
Design I-SKILL

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Gulp B-SKILL
, O
Compass B-SKILL
, O
SASS B-SKILL
, O
Symfony2 B-SKILL

Currently O
working O
as O
Senior B-PROF
Software I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
TeckPRO B-ORG

Yuliia B-PER
Kutsyk I-PER
is O
a O
Wordpress B-PROF
Back-end I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
based O
in O
Malta B-LOC

Software B-PROF
Tester I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Manual B-SKILL
QA I-SKILL
and O
Web B-SKILL
understanding I-SKILL
and O
Web/Desktop/Mobile B-SKILL
testing I-SKILL

Sviatoslav B-PER
worked O
as O
Web B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Bambuk B-ORG
Design I-ORG
Studio I-ORG
from O
Jan. B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
present I-DATE

PHP B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Gameloft B-ORG
from O
Oct B-DATE
2018 I-DATE
Jul I-DATE
2020 I-DATE

UX/UI B-PROF
Designer, I-PROF
Team I-PROF
Leader I-PROF
at O
Grinteq B-ORG
from O
MAY B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
DECEMBER I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Andriy B-PER
Marmuliak I-PER
from O
Lviv B-LOC

Pavlo B-PER
Lavrenenko I-PER
graduated O
from O
Chernihiv B-ORG
State I-ORG
Technological I-ORG
University I-ORG

Head B-PROF
of I-PROF
Product I-PROF

Alina B-PER
Karas, I-PER
PhD I-PER
from O
the B-LOC
USA I-LOC

MYTIAIEV B-PER
YEVHEN I-PER

Currently O
working O
as O
Business B-PROF
Analyst I-PROF
at O
Right&Above B-ORG

Sergej B-PER
Miroshnichenko I-PER
worked O
as O
Front-end B-PROF
developer I-PROF
at O
Naga B-ORG
from O
January B-DATE
2023 I-DATE
now I-DATE

OLEKSII B-PER
SUBBOTIN I-PER
worked O
as O
Entrepreneur B-PROF
at O
Tourpartner B-ORG

Experience O
: O
January B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
Present I-DATE

SULTAN B-PER
ISRAFILZADE I-PER
worked O
as O
PLANNING B-PROF
ENGINEER/PROJECT I-PROF
CONTROL I-PROF
SPECIALIST I-PROF
at O
STP B-ORG
(Sumgait I-ORG
Technologies I-ORG
Park) I-ORG

Worked O
at O
Merehead B-ORG
in O
Ukraine, B-LOC
Kiev I-LOC
01.2021–03.2022 B-DATE

Freelance B-PROF
at O
Web-vp B-ORG
from O
Sep B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
June I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Spring B-SKILL
, O
Lambda B-SKILL
, O
SNS B-SKILL
, O
Jenkins B-SKILL

Alexey B-PER
Diachenko I-PER
worked O
as O
Junior B-PROF
QA I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
at O
Hammer B-ORG
Truck I-ORG
from O
02.2021 B-DATE
02.2022 I-DATE

Studied O
at O
Odesa B-ORG
National I-ORG
Polytechnic I-ORG
University I-ORG

Danyl B-PER
Bulbas I-PER

Skills O
: O
Black B-SKILL
Box I-SKILL
Testing I-SKILL
, O
CI/CD B-SKILL
, O
SDLC B-SKILL
& I-SKILL
STLC I-SKILL
, O
HTML B-SKILL
5 I-SKILL
, O
Agile/Scrum/Kanban B-SKILL

SMM B-PROF
manager I-PROF

Currently O
working O
as O
Wordpress B-PROF
Back-end I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Ternala B-ORG

Дарья B-PER
Зенченко I-PER
worked O
as O
Email B-PROF
Marketing I-PROF
Specialist I-PROF
at O
ПАО B-ORG
«Актабанк» I-ORG

Anzhelika B-PER
Hordieieva I-PER
worked O
as O
Graphic B-PROF
Designer I-PROF
at O
NDA B-ORG

Skills O
: O
GIT B-SKILL
, O
CSS B-SKILL
, O
Maven B-SKILL
, O
Python B-SKILL
, O
Spring B-SKILL
Security I-SKILL

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Git B-SKILL
, O
Postman B-SKILL
, O
API B-SKILL
, O
QA B-SKILL
Automation I-SKILL

Zainab B-PER
Adewunmi I-PER
worked O
as O
Customer B-PROF
and I-PROF
Sales I-PROF
Representative I-PROF
at O
Genix B-ORG
COMPANY I-ORG
from O
October B-DATE
2019 I-DATE
May I-DATE
2020 I-DATE

Frontend B-PROF
developer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Gitlab B-SKILL
and O
Bootstrap B-SKILL
and O
Typescript B-SKILL

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Angular B-SKILL
, O
PHP B-SKILL
, O
OpenCart B-SKILL
, O
Laravel B-SKILL

Currently O
working O
as O
Data B-PROF
Scientist I-PROF
at O
KPMG B-ORG

Software B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
and I-PROF
VAS I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
CodeIgniter B-SKILL
and O
React.js B-SKILL
and O
MySQL B-SKILL

Currently O
working O
as O
Frontend B-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
PM-DT B-ORG

Experience O
: O
~1 B-DATE
year I-DATE

Regional B-PROF
Coordinator I-PROF
for I-PROF
Eastern I-PROF
Europe I-PROF

Oleh B-PER
Meserenko I-PER
from O
East B-LOC
Hanover, I-LOC
NJ I-LOC

Skills O
: O
Express B-SKILL
, O
PostgreSQL B-SKILL
, O
NestJS B-SKILL
, O
TypeScript B-SKILL
, O
Docker B-SKILL

IRYNA B-PER
HRESKO I-PER
worked O
as O
COPYWRITER B-PROF
at O
Goodvalley B-ORG
from O
June B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
November I-DATE
2020 I-DATE

AVETIS B-PER
ANANYAN I-PER
graduated O
from O
ARMENIAN B-ORG
STATE I-ORG
UNIVERSITY I-ORG
OF I-ORG
ECONOMICS I-ORG

Currently O
working O
as O
Manager B-PROF
of I-PROF
Sales I-PROF
at O
Biochem B-ORG
Zusatzstoffe I-ORG
Handels I-ORG

Experience O
: O
april B-DATE
2014 I-DATE
july I-DATE
2016 I-DATE

DARIA B-PER
STRILETS I-PER
is O
a O
MANUAL B-PROF
QA I-PROF
ENGINEER I-PROF
based O
in O
KHARKIV B-LOC

PROJECT B-PROF
COORDINATOR I-PROF

Skills O
: O
Prototype B-SKILL
, O
XD B-SKILL
, O
Figma B-SKILL
, O
Tilda B-SKILL
, O
CorelDRAW B-SKILL

Andrii B-PER
Kostenko I-PER
from O
Kyiv B-LOC

RUSLAN B-PER
VOLOVIK I-PER
from O
Kiev, B-LOC
remote I-LOC

Currently O
working O
as O
Product B-PROF
Designer I-PROF
at O
Practicum B-ORG
by I-ORG
Yandex I-ORG

Automation B-PROF
QA I-PROF
Engineer I-PROF
with O
skills O
in O
Allure B-SKILL
and O
Confluence B-SKILL
and O
TS B-SKILL

DIRECTOR B-PROF
OF I-PROF
SOFTWARE I-PROF
ENGINEERING I-PROF

Android B-PROF
Developer I-PROF

Freelance B-PROF
Web I-PROF
Developer I-PROF
at O
Malevich B-ORG
from O
NOVEMBER B-DATE
2020 I-DATE
AUGUST I-DATE
2021 I-DATE

SEO B-PROF
SPECIALIST I-PROF
at O
GDM B-ORG
GROUP I-ORG
from O
JANUARY B-DATE
2014 I-DATE
AUGUST I-DATE
2018 I-DATE

Skills O
: O
Linux B-SKILL
, O
HTML B-SKILL
+ I-SKILL
CSS I-SKILL
basics I-SKILL
, O
Agile B-SKILL
and I-SKILL
Waterfall I-SKILL
concept I-SKILL
knowledge I-SKILL
, O
API B-SKILL
testing I-SKILL
basics I-SKILL
, O
Manual B-SKILL
QA I-SKILL

Technical O
expertise O
: O
Waterfall B-SKILL
, O
Miro B-SKILL
, O
Trello B-SKILL
, O
Jira B-SKILL

Sales B-PROF
Manager I-PROF
practice I-PROF

Yuliia B-PER
Holtvyanska I-PER
worked O
as O
Senior B-PROF
Administrator I-PROF
at O
Clinic B-ORG
of I-ORG
Aesthetic I-ORG
Cosmetology I-ORG

Scrum B-PROF
Master I-PROF

Technical O
expertise O
: O
software B-SKILL
documentation I-SKILL
, O
testing B-SKILL
software I-SKILL
, O
Kanban B-SKILL
, O
Agile B-SKILL

Skills O
: O
Atlassian B-SKILL
stack I-SKILL
integration I-SKILL
(Jira+Confluence+Bitbucket+Bamboo) I-SKILL
, O
git B-SKILL
, O
monitoring B-SKILL
integration I-SKILL
(Nagios, I-SKILL
Zabbix, I-SKILL
Sensu, I-SKILL
Icinga2) I-SKILL
, O
databases B-SKILL
(MS I-SKILL
SQL\MySQL\PostgreSQL) I-SKILL
, O
Microsoft B-SKILL
Windows I-SKILL
